so we're going to talk about
所以我们要谈论
basically building spring applications
基本上建立Spring 应用
that integrate and it's called
整合在一起，这叫做
social integration but as we speak in a
社会融合，但正如我们所说的那样
minute it's gonna it's not necessarily
一分钟，那不一定
social don't get hung up on that word
社交不要被这个词挂断
I'll speak to why I'm in it but
我会说为什么我会在里面，但是
basically spring developers guide to
基本上春季开发人员指南
social integration building applications
社会融合建筑应用
that integrate with api's outside of
与api外部的集成
themselves
他们自己
I'm gonna make some statements later in
我稍后要发表一些声明
this talk and because of that they've
这次谈话，因此他们
asked me to put this so called safe
请我把这个所谓的安全
harbor statement in there to kind of
那里的港口声明
tell you that I might make statements
告诉你我可以发表声明
about things that are in progress I mean
关于正在进行中的事情
I'm no lawyer but basically it says
我不是律师，但基本上说
don't don't hold me to any of those
别抱着我
things there are just things that I
事情就是我的事情
would I would like to do but I can't
我想做但是我做不到
promise you they're gonna happen I'm
答应你，他们会发生的，我是
again I'm no lawyer so I've tried to
再次，我不是律师，所以我试图
kind of dumb this down for myself and
对于我自己来说这有点愚蠢，
hopefully it'll help you guys out as
希望它将对你们有帮助
well understand what this means and so I
很好理解这意味着什么，所以我
put in the John Lennon statement so this
放在约翰·列侬的声明中，这样
just basically means you know I'm making
基本上就是说你知道我在做
plans but life may change those so bear
计划，但生活可能会改变那些，所以忍受
with me when I start making
当我开始制作时和我在一起
forward-thinking plans or statements
前瞻性计划或声明
about what I might or might not do
关于我可能会或可能不会做的事情
alright so what's in a tweet I've put
好了，我在推文中写了什么
together a handful of tweets that I've
我在一起的一些推文
picked up over just the last several
拿起了最后几个
days just to kind of talk about you know
只是为了谈论您知道的日子
the kinds of things you might pull from
您可能会从中提取的东西
a social network now again I want to
现在我想再次建立一个社交网络
stress this is not necessarily about
强调这不一定
social but if you were working with
社交，但如果您与
social networks like Facebook or Twitter
社交网络，如Facebook或Twitter
or what-have-you
或你有什么
there's a lot of things you can learn
你可以学到很多东西
about your users and a lot of things you
关于您的用户以及您的很多事情
can learn about the the the people that
可以了解那些
they are friends with a lot of few
他们是很多人的朋友
things you can learn about I am it just
你可以学到的东西就是我
generally if you start searching Twitter
通常，如果您开始搜索Twitter
or searching Facebook and so here's Josh
或搜索Facebook，所以这里是Josh
long he travels a lot and apparently he
他长时间旅行很多，显然他
left Tokyo Shanghai and oz Lo and then
离开了上海东京和oz Lo，然后
he came here if I were as if I was a
他来我这里就像是我
business that was somehow in any way
某种程度上的生意
whatsoever related to the travel
与旅行有关的任何事情
industry and I saw this tweet I might
行业，我看到了这则推文
want to react to that and maybe
想对此做出反应，也许
entice Josh to purchase my products or
诱使乔希购买我的产品或
buy my services right if you know by my
如果您知道我的话，请购买我的服务
luggage or use my airline or whatever it
行李或使用我的航空公司或其他任何东西
is you might do if you saw this kind of
如果您看到这种情况，您可能会做
thing it's
事情是
it'd be really cool if I could write an
如果我能写一个
application that would follow or just
后续的应用程序
follow this these this stream of
遵循这些这些流
information that people are freely
人们自由的信息
providing on the Internet
在互联网上提供
it'd be cool if I could write an
如果我能写一个会很酷
application that would follow that and
遵循的应用程序和
somehow figure out what this tweet means
以某种方式弄清楚这条推文意味着什么
and what's trying to be said and from
以及试图说些什么
that react to it
对它做出反应
here's another one venkat says a little
这是另一个venkat说了一点
bit about modularization and what's
关于模块化的一些知识
testable and again the same kind of
可测试的，同样是
thing if you were a developer and you
如果您是开发人员并且您
wanted to you know react to certain
想知道你对某些事情有反应
statements you might if you were very
您可能会发表声明
clever the big cats is a little bit
聪明的大猫有点
harder to you know programmatically
以编程方式更难了解
discern but you could maybe figure out
辨别，但您可能会发现
what Vinc has trying to say here and
Vinc在这里试图说什么，
from that react to it maybe repost it to
从它的反应也许重新发布到
a friend of to of of I'm sorry tweet a
的of的朋友，对不起，推特
collection of friends who are also
也是
developers you might find value into
您可能会发现价值的开发人员
this just the same way you do manually
这与您手动执行的方式相同
maybe with your your phone you might
也许用您的手机可能
have an automated system that might kind
有一个可能有点友善的自动化系统
of do the same kind of thing if you
如果您做同样的事情
could somehow learn something about it
可以以某种方式学到一些东西
and then my colleague Roy apparently
然后我的同事罗伊
wanted a taco emoji so clearly we need
想要炸玉米饼表情符号，所以很明显我们需要
to tart we need to market tacos to Roy
要t，我们需要向罗伊销售炸玉米饼
he wants some tacos not just an emoji
他想要一些玉米饼而不只是表情符号
but as long as he's mentioning tacos I
但只要他提到炸玉米饼我
imagine he likes eating them so let's
想像他喜欢吃它们，所以让我们
let's do that and here's what one of my
让我们这样做，这就是我的其中之一
own I put this in at the last minute
我自己在最后一刻把它放进去
just because this really happened to me
只是因为这真的发生在我身上
there's a place I I like to eat in in
有个我喜欢在里面吃饭的地方
Texas called Torchy's tacos and Torchy's
得克萨斯州称为Torchy的玉米饼和Torchy的玉米饼
is outstanding tacos I'm not doing an
是出色的玉米饼，我没有
advertisement for them or anything I'm
为他们或我做的任何事情做广告
just stating a clear fact they are
只是说明一个明显的事实，他们是
outstanding and but I was there the
优秀，但我在那里
other night and the service was really
前一天晚上，服务真的
slow and people were telling us it was
慢，人们告诉我们这是
taking over an hour to get the food and
花一个多小时拿到食物和
that's never happened before and so I
那从来没有发生过，所以我
just tweeted about it and so the next
刚刚发了推文，所以下一个
day Torchy's responded and said no we're
一天，托奇回应并说不，我们是
not we're gonna deal with that so if as
不，我们将要处理，所以如果
a business if you were able to respond
如果您能够回应企业
to your customer is not I'm sure they
对您的客户不是我确定他们
don't have a system doing this I'm sure
我确定没有系统这样做
they have someone sitting around who's
他们周围有人坐
in charge of social media but if there's
负责社交媒体，但如果有
a way you could somehow understand the
一种可以以某种方式理解
fact that I was upset about my weight I
我对自己的体重感到沮丧我
mean clearly the word tacos were in
清楚地意味炸玉米饼在其中
there and there was a indication of time
那里有时间的指示
and not only just an indication of time
不只是时间的指示
there was a measure of time that would
有一定的时间可以
probably indicate a long wait that
可能表示漫长的等待
might be something that a system could
可能是系统可以
respond to and say you know what I think
回应说你知道我的想法
I understand what that said that what
我明白那是什么意思
that's saying well what I'm gonna ask
这就是说我要问的
you to do now before we go any further
您现在就要做，然后再继续
is I'm going to invite you to be as much
我要邀请你成为
a part of my session demo as you
您的我的会话演示的一部分
possibly can so as often as you feel
可能会尽可能多地
like it tweet during this session and be
喜欢在本届会议期间发推文并成为
sure and use either this well be sure
确定并使用任一此确定
and use the spring social tag for sure
并确定使用春季社交标签
but also at least Jews STG exit tag or
而且至少还有犹太人STG出口标签或
mention at spring 1/2 GX because it's
在GX春季1/2提及，因为
kind of important for the for the
对于...来说很重要
purposes of this this demo I'm gonna
这个演示的目的是
show you later and you'll see what I'm
以后告诉你，你会看到我
talking about when we get there so we
谈论我们何时到达那里，所以我们
hear a lot about micro services this
听到很多关于微服务的信息
weekend at spring one a lot of people
春天的周末很多人
talking about micro-services and
谈论微服务和
generally speaking when we talking about
一般来说，当我们谈论
micro-services we're talking about
我们正在谈论的微服务
building applications that are composed
构建组成的应用程序
of multiple individual services and they
多个个人服务，他们
they communicate these components
他们传达这些成分
communicate with each other and
互相交流
coordinate with each other to accomplish
互相配合以完成
some sort of business need but what
某种业务需求，但是
we're gonna talk about in this session
我们将在本节中讨论
is related but different it's it's how
是相关的，但不同的是
do you reach out to some other service
你会联系其他服务吗
outside of your your little bubble your
在你的小泡泡外面
applications bubble of serv micro
serv micro的应用泡沫
services and how do you reach out to
服务以及您如何联系
those and either fetch data alter data
这些和要么获取数据，要么更改数据
what have you and turns out there's III
你有什么，结果是
say there's hundreds honestly I've never
说真的有数百人我从来没有
counted I would imagine there's probably
算了，我想可能有
thousands of API is out there on the
上千种API
internet chock full of information
充满信息的互联网
things you can do with them things you
你可以和他们一起做的事情
can read from them and things you can
可以从他们那里读到东西
learn from and most of these not all but
从中学习，大部分不是，而是
most of these are secured with OAuth and
其中大多数通过OAuth和
if anybody's ever worked with Olaf you
如果有人曾经与Olaf合作过
know that OAuth is it a it's a tricky
知道OAuth是一个棘手的问题
little beast and not necessarily easy to
小兽，不一定容易
work with and that's what we're we're
与我们合作，这就是我们
gonna have to overcome if we're gonna
如果我们要克服的话
just work with these api's it would be
只需使用这些api就可以了
nice if we could just call a method or
如果我们可以调用一个方法或
send a get request and things would just
发送获取请求，事情只会
work but unfortunately those api's make
工作，但不幸的是那些api的
it tricky well fortunately for the users
幸运的是，它对用户来说很棘手
of those api's they're secure but that
这些api中的它们是安全的，但是
security and therefore makes it trickier
安全性，因此变得棘手
to work with and so this is this is a
与合作，所以这是一个
summary of what Olaf is
奥拉夫是什么的摘要
you've never seen it before it is an
你从未见过它是一个
authorization protocol not
授权协议不
authentication authorization although
虽然认证授权
there are there are means about which
有关于
you can use it to authenticate a user
您可以使用它来认证用户
essentially what it is your app
本质上是您的应用程序
application needs access needs to read
应用程序需要访问需要阅读
or write data to some other or users
或向其他人或用户写入数据
data on some other API so you have
其他API上的数据
something like Facebook let's say or
比方说Facebook之类的东西
Twitter and you would like to read their
Twitter，您想阅读他们的
tweets or you'd like to post the tweet
鸣叫，或者您想发布鸣叫
on their behalf and you need that you
代表他们，你需要你
need their permission to do that it
需要他们的许可才能这样做
would be really nice if Twitter just
如果Twitter只是真的会很好
didn't let people post for them without
没有让人们为他们张贴
their permission
他们的许可
I mean it's good if they lock that down
我的意思是如果他们把它锁定下来是很好的
so you need to get permission to do that
因此您需要获得许可才能执行此操作
the way you get permission is using
您获得许可的方式是使用
OAuth this thing called the OAuth dance
OAuth这个东西叫做OAuth舞蹈
and what it generally involves is a
它通常涉及的是
redirect from your application to the to
从您的应用程序重定向到
the API involved to an authorization
授权涉及的API
page where the user assuming they're
用户假定他们所在的页面
logged in and if not they will be logged
登录，否则将被登录
in if they're logged into Twitter
如果他们已登录Twitter
Facebook LinkedIn whatever they can say
他们可以说的Facebook LinkedIn
yes I will allow this application to
是的，我将允许该应用程序
access this information on my behalf and
代表我访问此信息，并
and the problem with OAuth though is it
和OAuth的问题是
comes in so many flavors
有很多口味
there's OAuth 1 and oauth 1.0 a which
有OAuth 1和oauth 1.0
were subtly different from each other
彼此有细微的差别
one doll a fixed a small security hole
一个娃娃固定一个小安全孔
in 1.0 but unfortunately believe it or
在1.0中，但不幸的是相信它，或者
not there are still api is out there
那里还没有api
that are still using OAuth 1 and then
仍在使用OAuth 1然后
there's a lot too which has its own
还有很多也有它自己的
multiple flavors there's the most common
多种口味最常见
when you run into his authorization
当您遇到他的授权时
grant what essentially amounts to is
授予本质上等于
it's a lot like olaf 1 your application
这很像olaf 1您的应用程序
redirects to the provider the provider
重定向到提供者
asks the user if it's okay that they use
询问用户是否可以使用
your data you say yes it redirects back
您的数据，您说是的，它将重定向回
and when it redirects back it redirects
当它重定向回到它重定向
back with an authorization code and this
返回授权码和这个
code can then be used behind the scenes
然后可以在后台使用代码
to exchange with the provider and get a
与提供者交换并获得
thing called an access token if this
如果这是所谓的访问令牌
access token represents the permission
访问令牌代表权限
the authorization that the user has
用户拥有的授权
given you to access and manipulate their
给你访问和操纵他们的
data implicit grants kind of like that
数据隐式授予类似于
it still does the redirect but instead
它仍然执行重定向，但是
of getting a code back
找回代码的过程
you actually get the access token back
您实际上获得了访问令牌
it's it's more useful in scenarios where
这在以下情况下更有用
you you don't really want to deal with
你你真的不想对付
the the overhead of redirecting and then
重定向的开销，然后
turning around and calling around
转身打电话
calling back again it's it's useful in
再次回叫它是有用的
scenarios where you can't trust the
您无法信任的情况
client to necessarily maintain that that
客户必须坚持认为
token securely long-term it's good
令牌可以长期安全地很好
primarily for clients that's where it's
主要针对客户所在的地方
mostly useful for and then there's
最有用的，然后有
resource owner credentials grant also
资源所有者凭据授予也
known as password grant this enables the
称为密码授予，可以启用
client to simply ask the user for their
客户只是向用户询问他们的
username and password and the exchange
用户名和密码以及交换
that those credentials for an access
那些凭证用于访问
token it's it's it's a little different
令牌，这是有点不同
than what they might do if you were
比他们做的事还要多
using HTTP basic where the client would
使用HTTP基本客户端
ask the user for their credentials and
向用户询问其凭据，并
it would encode those credentials and
它将对那些凭据进行编码，
use them on every single request this is
在每个单独的请求上使用它们
a little different in that it asks the
有点不同，它要求
client for their credentials exchanges
客户进行凭证交换
those for our pasts are for a token and
那些过去的东西是为了象征
then uses that token on every single
然后在每一个上使用该令牌
request it's expected to toss away the
要求将其扔掉
credentials after it's done this is
完成后的凭据是
actually more appropriate for like you
实际上更适合像你这样的人
know high high trust scenarios where
知道哪里有高信任度的场景
like a mobile phone mobile application
就像手机的移动应用
where a redirect would be either awkward
重定向会很尴尬
or perhaps impossible and you the user
也许是不可能的，而您是用户
actually does trust the client to a high
实际上确实信任客户很高
degree and it's interesting that they're
学位，有趣的是
not going to use their credentials
不会使用他们的凭据
inappropriately and then there's client
不适当地，然后有客户
credentials grant which is a lot like
凭证授予很像
password grant the only difference is
密码授予的唯一区别是
instead of exchanging a user's
而不是交换用户的
credentials for access token you're
您使用的访问令牌的凭据
exchanging clients credentials the
交换客户凭证
actual applications credentials for an
的实际应用程序凭证
access token and the one thing about
访问令牌和一件事
that that's kind of important as you're
那就像你一样重要
limited what you get the token you get
限制您获得的令牌
can't be used to alter a user's set of
不能用于更改用户的
data or to even access necessarily a
数据甚至访问必不可少的
user set of data it's very limited to
用户数据集仅限于
application level type top operations
应用程序级别类型的顶级操作
but regardless of which one of these you
但是不管你是哪一个
use where do you get this access token
使用您从哪里获得此访问令牌
back and you might in some cases get a
返回，在某些情况下您可能会得到
refresh token back in the case of OAuth
如果是OAuth，请刷新令牌
1 you're going to get an access token
1您将获得访问令牌
back and you're gonna get a set of
回来，你会得到一套
secrets back that go with that you have
你拥有的秘密
these things now what are you going to
这些东西现在你打算怎么办
do with those because you're expected to
与那些做，因为你应该
store them securely and so you if you
安全地存储它们，所以如果您
were to write this yourself if you were
如果你是
to build this up at an application
在应用程序上构建
yourself you have to not only figure out
你自己，你不仅要弄清楚
how to negotiate the OAuth dance but
如何协商OAuth舞蹈，但是
once you're done you have to figure out
一旦完成，就必须弄清楚
what you're gonna do with those
你该怎么办
credentials what you're gonna do with
凭证您将要做什么
that token primarily that token and
该令牌主要是该令牌和
those keys okay so that they don't fall
那些键还可以，这样它们就不会掉下来
into the wrong hands you're gonna have
掌握在错误的手里
to store them securely and figure out a
安全地存储它们并找出
plan for how you're gonna deal with that
计划如何处理
and how you're going to associate that
以及如何将其关联
token with a specific user because that
具有特定用户的令牌，因为
token does belong to that user if you
令牌确实属于该用户，如果您
have another user authorize you get yet
有另一个用户授权您得到
another token so you have to save this
另一个令牌，所以您必须保存此令牌
stuff securely and associate it with the
安全地将其与
user in question
有问题的用户
let's our Spring social my project comes
让我们的春季社交活动我的项目来
in and so what spring social does it
在什么春季社交活动中
solves all those those interesting
解决所有那些有趣的事情
problems it handles that OAuth dance and
它处理OAuth跳舞和
it knows whether you're dealing with
它知道你是否正在与
OAuth 1 or OAuth 2 it knows how to which
OAuth 1或OAuth 2，它知道如何
one you're dealing with because the the
您正在处理的一个，因为
way it knows is which provider are you
它知道您是哪个提供商的方式
dealing with you're dealing with Twitter
与您打交道
you're dealing with OAuth 1 0 a if
您正在使用OAuth 1 0 a if
you're dealing with Facebook you're
你正在和Facebook打交道
dealing with OAuth 2 or at least
处理OAuth 2或至少
Facebook's variant of OAuth 2 if you're
如果您是Facebook的OAuth 2变体
dealing with LinkedIn you have the
与LinkedIn打交道，你有
choice between the two but but spring
两者之间的选择，但春天
social implements the OAuth 2 option so
社交实施OAuth 2选项，因此
it just knows that if you're dealing
它只是知道如果您要交易
with this particular provider this
与这个特定的提供商
particular API this is the kind of OAuth
特定的API，这是OAuth的一种
dance you need to work with thing is you
跳舞，你需要与事物合作是你
don't have to worry about it you don't
不必担心，您不必
have to go write a controller to do this
必须去写一个控制器来做到这一点
redirect nonsense you don't have to
重定向废话，你不必
write anything to fetch that token under
写任何东西来获取该令牌
the covers spring socials going to
封面春季社会去
handle that for you and it does know how
为您处理，它确实知道如何
once you have this token it knows how to
一旦拥有此令牌，它就会知道如何
store it we have a have it something
存放它，我们有东西
called a what's it called Val a
叫什么叫Val a
connection repository and so a
连接存储库等
connection in spring social terms is a
春季社交用语中的联系是
representation of that authorization
该授权的表示
it's not just the token but it's
这不仅是令牌，而是
anything that goes with the token that
令牌附带的任何东西
identifies this as the authorization
将其标识为授权
that the user has given you and we we
用户给了你，我们
store that and we store it securely
存储，我们将其安全存储
our current implementations out of the
我们目前的实现
boxes we have an in-memory one which is
盒子，我们有一个内存中的
not very useful except for development
除了开发以外，不是很有用
purposes we also have one that hits a
目的，我们也有一个击中
relational database using JDBC there are
使用JDBC的关系数据库
some community contributions that do
一些社区的贡献
things like Mongo and neo4j so if you
像Mongo和neo4j这样的东西，如果你
wanna store those there it's actually
想把那些存储在那里
comes down to a very simple interface
归结为一个非常简单的界面
you
您
people met and you can create your own
人们见面，您可以创建自己的
it does provide several out-of-the-box
它确实提供了几个现成的
bindings API bindings where a binding
绑定API绑定，其中绑定
what this is primarily is a a set of
这主要是一组
like a template type class that just
就像模板类型类
knows how to work with that API and
知道如何使用该API并
those the individual operations and the
那些个人操作和
parameters that need to be sent in those
那些需要发送的参数
what needs to be returned and it
什么需要退还，它
includes with that a set of domain
包括一组域名
objects that are bound and to whatever
绑定对象以及任何对象
the API is going to return back so you
API将返回，因此您
don't have to deal with this yourself
不必自己处理
you don't have to make a rest template
您不必制作休息模板
call and then somehow create a domain
呼叫，然后以某种方式创建域
object at that rest templates gonna bind
其余对象将绑定
the data to you we provide that for a
我们为您提供的数据
handful of these Facebook and Twitter
这些Facebook和Twitter中的少数
primarily are the two that I'm really
主要是我真正的两个
focused on LinkedIn to a lesser degree
在较小程度上专注于LinkedIn
for historical reasons we also support
由于历史原因，我们也支持
TripIt and github
TripIt和github
TripIt specifically I'll talk about a
具体来说，我将谈论
little bit later I've sort of shelved
不久之后，我被搁置了
hoping that somebody in the community
希望社区中有人
will step up and run with it and if
将加紧并运行它，如果
nobody does then apparently it wasn't
没有人这样做显然不是
that valuable to anybody it was there
对任何人都有价值的东西
primarily as a driver for some specific
主要是作为一些特定的驱动程序
functionality as a trip it originally
最初的旅行功能
implemented and now TripIt does not do
已实施，现在TripIt无法执行
that anymore
那个了
and as a consequence it's not helping me
结果并没有帮助我
except making my life miserable when I
除了使我的生活悲惨
have to support yet another API advising
必须支持另一种API建议
github we're probably gonna keep around
github我们可能会继续
for a while because there's actually a
有一阵子，因为实际上
lot of value in providing github github
提供github github的巨大价值
connectivity especially if you ever use
连接性，尤其是如果您使用过
spring Daioh our our website if you ever
如果您愿意的话，春天大oh我们的网站
visit it there's a lot of spring social
参观那里有很多春季社交活动
github under the covers in there and so
那里的掩盖下的github等等
I sort of need to support that in order
我有点需要为了支持
to just support spring that i/o but
只是支持春天，我/但
there's a lot of community projects and
有很多社区项目，
I'll talk more about those here in a
我会在这里更多地谈论这些
moment
时刻
but the one thing I do want to stress is
但我要强调的一件事是
even though the project name is named
即使项目名称已命名
spring social that's a horrible name I
春季社交，这是一个可怕的名字
wish it was not named that in hindsight
希望事后发现它没有被命名
I wish it was named something else and
我希望它被命名为别的
maybe someday I'll get to rename it
也许有一天我会重命名它
right now it's still called social I
现在它仍然被称为社交我
want to call it spring Connect connect
想称其为Spring Connect connect
makes sense to me because that's what
对我来说很有意义，因为那是
we're doing is we're connecting your
我们正在做的是我们正在连接您的
application with another API but the
带有其他API的应用程序，但
point to prove the point that it's not
证明这一点不是
just social we have a handful of and
只是社交，我们有几个
there's more than this but there's a
不仅限于此，还有一个
just three here that I've pulled out
我抽出的只有三个
that I might point out that spring
我可能会指出那个春天
social does have integration for it does
社会确实有整合
have support for
有支持
at least through if not not from me but
至少通过不是不是我而是
through community projects that are very
通过非常重要的社区项目
non social in nature first off we have a
非社会性质首先我们有一个
eco beat so it could be the spring
生态节拍，所以可能是春天
social Iike bee project interestingly
有趣的社交Iike蜜蜂项目
enough was written by one of the guys on
其中一个人写的足够
the spring team but he he wrote it no
The Spring Team ，但他他写了没有
official capacity he did it as just a
他的官方身份是
fun exercise and so don't consider it
有趣的运动，所以不要考虑它
supported in any way but in fact he
以任何方式支持，但事实上他
would he would like me to tell you about
他想让我告诉你有关
it because he would like people to pick
这是因为他希望人们选择
up and kind of help him maintain and
和帮助他维持和
develop it but it helps him control
开发它，但是它可以帮助他控制
thermostats in his house these little
这些小房子里的温控器
smart thermostats and it interestingly
智能恒温器，有趣的是
enough these thermostats are secured
这些恒温器已足够固定
with OAuth and he can connect to these
使用OAuth，他可以连接到这些
thermostats through OAuth using spring
Spring 通过OAuth通过恒温器
social and he can get all sorts of
社交，他可以得到各种各样的
interesting information about kind of
有关种类的有趣信息
you know what the the temperatures are
你知道温度是多少
in the home currently I think he I think
目前在家里我想他我想
he's implemented the stuff where you can
他在可能的地方实施了这些东西
kind of see a trend of the temperatures
看到温度的趋势
I don't believe he's implemented where
我不相信他在哪里实施
you can actually set the thermostat
您实际上可以设置恒温器
through the API but I do believe it is
通过API，但我相信这是
possible to do that I just don't think
可能做到这一点，我只是不认为
he's done that yet and so I wouldn't
他已经做到了，所以我不会
consider this a social API I probably
认为这是我的社交API
wouldn't want my friends changing the
不想让我的朋友改变
thermostat in my house I have enough
我家里的恒温器我有足够的
problem with that when my family comes
我家人来的时候有什么问题
to visit I don't really want this to let
去参观，我真的不想让这个
the wider world do this so that's not
更广泛的世界这样做是为了
really a social API yes spring social is
确实是社交API，是春季社交
used to to do this there's nothing
过去经常这样做
called wunderlist which help it's a
叫做奇妙清单，这是一个
strange little app that basically is the
奇怪的小应用程序，基本上是
I you know we all implement to-do list
我知道我们都执行待办事项清单
applications as demos right yeah
作为演示应用程序是的
somebody's actually done it and deployed
实际上有人完成并部署了
it and so this is what essentially what
它，所以这实际上是什么
wunderlist is is these to-do lists and
奇妙清单就是这些待办事项清单，
reminders and errands and I wouldn't
提醒和差事，我不会
consider that social I mean less you're
认为社交，我的意思是说你更少
sharing these to-do lists with other
与其他人共享这些待办事项清单
people but wonder list we have a spring
人，但奇迹清单我们有一个春天
social wonder list for doing that and
这样做的社会奇迹清单
then github and bitbucket now you might
然后github和bitbucket现在你可能
argue github is a social network and to
认为github是一个社交网络，
some degree it is and you can follow me
在某种程度上，你可以跟随我
you can follow my projects as far when
你什么时候可以关注我的项目
it comes to coding github is referred to
谈到编码github是指
oftentimes as social coding because we
通常作为社交编码，因为我们
socially code together through this
通过此社交代码
repository but
仓库但是
if you step back a little bit it's it's
如果你退后一点，那是
just a source code repository and so
只是一个源代码库，所以
github has an API that's secured with
github的API受保护
OAuth we have spring social github for
OAuth，我们有春季社交github
that same thing with bitbucket we have
Bitbucket也有同样的事情
spring social plugin that a community
春季社交插件社区
member is written for working with
成员是为与
bitbucket
比特桶
again I wouldn't consider those social
再次，我不会考虑那些社交
networks but there you go there's also I
网络，但你去那里也有我
don't have it listed here but spring
春天没在这里列出
social Salesforce I really don't
我真的不喜欢社交Salesforce
consider my finances or are not
考虑我的财务状况
salesforce at my uh not finances my
我的Salesforce不能资助我
sales calls and my whatever else
销售电话和其他
salesforce does I don't use Salesforce
我不使用Salesforce
so I'm just guessing but I don't
所以我只是在猜测，但我没有
consider that a social network yet there
认为那里还存在一个社交网络
you have it and then one other is
你有它，然后另一个是
Quicken there's spring social into it
加快春天的社交活动
has gives you access to ebooks re
使您可以重新访问电子书
quickbooks online I wouldn't consider my
在线速记本我不会考虑
finances a social network kind of
资助一种社交网络
problem and yet spring social will
问题，但春天的社会意愿
integrate with those you have a question
与您有疑问的人融合
what what okay so the question is why
怎么样，所以问题是为什么
would I why can't I just go integrate
我为什么不能不去整合
with as myself is for any other any API
与其他任何其他API一样
out there and the answer to that is what
在那里，答案是什么
you sure you can
你确定你可以
the thing is spring social takes away
事情是春季社交活动夺走了
the need for you to to develop the
您需要发展
pieces of your application that deal
您的应用程序的一部分
with the OAuth dance in deal with the
用OAuth舞蹈处理
tokens you get and deal with refreshing
您获得并处理刷新的令牌
those tokens if they expire
这些令牌如果过期
you don't worry about that you just
你不用担心你只是
worry about using the API and it's but
担心使用API​​，但是
that may become a little bit more clear
可能会变得更加清晰
when we get around to seeing some of the
当我们四处看看
example code here in a minute cuz you're
只需一分钟，这里的示例代码
gonna be shocked at how little code I
我会为我的代码太少而感到震惊
have whether you should integrate it at
是否应该将其集成在
all I
我所有
there is no criteria for me for me I
我对我没有任何标准
have a very finite list of things I'm
我的事情清单很有限
gonna maintain primarily because I want
会主要因为我想要
to I want to focus on the core not so
我想不专注于核心
much on the API bindings I want the
我想要很多关于API绑定的信息
community to step forward and do the API
社区向前迈进并开发API
bindings and so in those cases the
绑定，因此在这些情况下
criteria to decide whether or not you
决定你是否的标准
want to add that comes down to do you
想要添加下来就可以做到
need it if your application needs it and
如果您的应用程序需要它，并且
there's not one already out there you
那里还没有人
should do this because if you need it
应该这样做，因为如果您需要
maybe somebody else will come along and
也许有人会来
eat it too and so that's what it comes
也吃它，这就是它的来
down to in some cases I will I will
在某些情况下，我会
admit in some of these community cases
在某些社区案例中承认
it did come down to just geeky interest
它确实归结为令人讨厌的兴趣
they wanted to see if they could do it
他们想看看是否能做到
but real realistically it comes down to
但实际上，它归结为
are you going to need this API do you
您需要这个API吗？
want to mess with implementing the
想要搞乱实施
entire Roth scenario yourself or would
整个Roth场景，您自己或
you rather just focus on the
你宁愿只专注于
connectivity and using the API in that
连接性和使用API
case that that's why you would do it
这就是为什么你会这样做的原因
you're asking why Google is why is there
你在问为什么Google在那
why is Google in a community lead
为什么Google在社区中处于领先地位
project for spring social as opposed to
春季社交项目，而不是
an official one it comes down to again I
官方的它归结为我
I don't I want to focus on the it comes
我不想专注于它的来临
down to two reasons really initially
最初有两个原因
when I first started this project there
当我第一次在那里开始这个项目时
was no large-scale Google API there was
没有大规模的Google API
several individual Google API is but
几个单独的Google API只是
nothing major and then we wanted to
没什么大不了的，然后我们想
focus primarily on the core and we
专注于核心，我们
needed a handful of API bindings such as
需要少量的API绑定，例如
Facebook and Twitter to kind of drive
Facebook和Twitter推动
out some of the functionality so that's
淘汰了一些功能，所以
why we developed those Google came along
为什么我们开发那些Google
especially with Google Plus that's when
特别是在使用Google Plus的时候
suddenly people that interested in
突然有兴趣的人
Google and they started building started
谷歌，他们开始建设开始
providing these api's and the community
提供这些api和社区
steps forward and said and at one time I
向前走说，一次我
was thinking yeah I would like to do
在想，我想做
Google+ I would like to do a Google API
Google+我想做一个Google API
binding but the community stepped up the
具有约束力，但社区加强了
community took it and they ran with it
社区接过了，他们跑了
and we've let them granted as tends to
并且我们已经让他们按照趋势
be the case in the community sometimes
有时在社区中是这样
there was grow cobwebs but we let them
有成长的蜘蛛网，但我们让他们
do that and at the end of the day again
这样做并在一天结束时再次
my bandwidth is terribly limited the
我的带宽非常有限
other guys on the team who contribute to
团队中其他为
this their bandwidth is terribly limited
这是他们的带宽非常有限
we decided to focus more on the core and
我们决定将重点更多地放在核心
just kind of maintain a couple of API
只是维护几个API
bindings and then let the community
绑定，然后让社区
drive the rest the thinking there is if
驱使其他人思考是否
it's important to the community the
对社区来说很重要
community will step up and do it if it's
社区将加紧努力，如果
not important to the community they
对社区不重要
won't Google is a special case also in a
谷歌在特殊情况下也不会
Google has a crap-ton of api's and
Google有很多api和
they're all sort of related and then
它们都是相关的，然后
also sort of distinct from each other it
也彼此不同
would be nice if you know maybe you had
如果您知道也许您会
individually you know there's this
个别地，你知道这是
debate that kind of even between me and
甚至在我和
some of the other community members
其他一些社区成员
who've worked on it should you have one
谁曾为它工作过
monster or Google API binding or should
Monster或Google API绑定或应该
you have a whole bunch of little ones
你有一堆小孩子
and there's benefit either way it's a
无论哪种方式都有好处
trade-off either way and that honestly I
权衡取舍，说实话我
want to let the community decide that I
想让社区决定我
don't want to do that myself so our
不想自己做，所以我们
focus now is the court and okay a couple
现在重点是法院，好吧，一对夫妇
of API bindings that just kind of help
API绑定只是一种帮助
us drive out things there but primarily
我们把东西赶出去，但主要是
as and I'm going to talk more to this a
作为，我将对此进行更多讨论
little bit later I'd really like
稍后我真的很想
to do a whole lot of the the work around
做很多的工作
individual api's alright so here's the
个别api没问题，所以这是
spring social project family and here's
春季社会项目家庭，这是
how it's more or less structured we have
它的结构或多或少
three social if you go into the if you
如果你进入三个社会
look in github and see how the projects
看看github看看项目如何
are structured you're gonna see the the
结构化，您将看到
main spring social project and within
春季主要社会项目及内部
that we have four sub projects there's
我们有四个子项目
the core which just provides very basic
只是提供非常基本的核心
stuff it includes an OAuth
包含OAuth的内容
implementation an OAuth template for
实施用于的OAuth模板
both Oh F 1 and O 2 and you can use
Oh F 1和O 2都可以使用
those you're free to use those directly
那些您可以自由直接使用的
if you want you generally don't need to
如果您愿意，通常不需要
there's a couple of cases when they come
有一些情况下，当他们来
in handy but generally you don't need to
方便，但是通常您不需要
use those directly unless you want to
除非您想直接使用这些
then there's spring social web I'm gonna
然后是春天的社交网站
go ahead and skip over to that when it's
继续并跳过它
being social web builds on top of the
社交网络建立在
core to give you that Oh auth dance that
核心给你哦auth跳舞
set of redirects that you can use to
您可以使用的一组重定向
redirect to a provider to come back and
重定向到提供程序以返回并
it's going to handle this for you
它会为你处理
essentially it provides a handful of
本质上，它提供了少数
controllers at a handful of filters for
几个过滤器的控制器
accomplishing a certain set of tasks
完成某些任务
around connectivity there's spring
连通性周围有春天
Social Security which aside from the
除了社会保障
fact that it has this fun little social
事实上，它有这个有趣的小社交
security phrase in there it offers an
那里的安全短语提供了一个
extension beyond what spring social web
超越春天的社交网络
offers when it comes to doing sign-in
提供登录时的优惠
with it essentially provides a fairly
基本上提供了一个相当
tight integration between spring
Spring 之间的紧密结合
security and spring social so that if
安全和春季社交，如果
you are doing this sign in with Facebook
您正在使用Facebook登录
sign in with Twitter it's it's fairly
用Twitter登录就可以了
tightly integrated with spring security
与Spring 安全性紧密集成
itself as opposed to there's another
本身，而不是另一个
similar feature that's part of web
网络中的类似功能
that's not tight with spring security
Spring 安全性并不严格
it's more agnostic to what your security
与您的安全性无关
layer is so we'll talk more about those
层，所以我们将更多地讨论那些
here in a bit and then there's spring
在这里，然后有春天
social config which was you don't use
您不使用的社​​交配置
necessarily directly but it was born
一定是直接的，但它是天生的
here a couple of releases ago to make it
在这里发布了几个版本
easier to configure spring social easier
更容易配置spring社交，更容易
to work with it what happened is in the
与它一起工作发生了什么事
initial version of spring social there
那里的春季社交的初始版本
you had to write a lot of xml
你不得不写很多xml
configuration in spring just to make
在春季配置只是为了
things work we made that better with
事情运作得更好，
both an XML namespace and Java config
XML名称空间和Java配置
support and built on top of all of that
支持并建立在所有这些之上
we have the provider bindings that
我们有提供者绑定
currently we support Facebook and
目前，我们支持Facebook和
Twitter LinkedIn github and I put a
Twitter LinkedIn github和我放了一个
question mark by TripIt I might even put
TripIt可能会问的问题
a question mark by LinkedIn these are
LinkedIn的问号是
ones that we created again primarily to
我们再次创建的那些主要是
drive out features in the core I'm kind
淘汰我所喜欢的核心功能
of gonna put I think put the word we
我想说的是
wanted to put as a put it in the ice box
想放到冰盒里
or put it in the shelf for LinkedIn and
或放在LinkedIn的书架上，
trip it and hope the community will step
绊倒它，希望社区能够迈出第一步
forward help us but we're not gonna
向前帮助我们，但我们不会
spend a great deal of time supporting
花大量时间支持
those directly github I'm gonna have to
那些直接github我必须
Facebook and Twitter I'm gonna have to
Facebook和Twitter，我将不得不
but everything else we're hoping the
但我们希望其他一切
community will step forward and then
社区将前进，然后
there's this other box and this was
还有另一个盒子，这是
updated as far as I know this is a
据我所知，这是一个更新
complete story but unfortunately not
完整的故事，但不幸的是没有
everybody tells me everything I have to
每个人都告诉我我必须做的一切
learn about a few things kind of on my
了解一些关于我的事情
own and but as far as I know this is a
拥有，但据我所知这是一个
complete set of the community
完整的社区
contributions to spring socials so we
对春季社交活动的贡献，所以我们
have stuff in there for all sorts of
里面有各种东西
things if you want to do photography you
你想摄影的事情
got 500px and you got Flickr you got
有500px，你有Flickr，你有
Instagram if you're we have a Foursquare
Instagram，如果你是我们的Foursquare
which I'm not really sure how that plays
我不太确定怎么玩
into how Foursquare keeps changing what
进入Foursquare如何不断改变
their business model is but we have as I
他们的商业模式是，但是我们和我一样
mentioned Intuit and QuickBooks Online
提到Intuit和QuickBooks Online
that's on there for the non social type
对于非社交类型而言
stuff there's AB dotnet there's all
东西有AB点网有
sorts of stuff there's things on here
各种各样的东西在这里
I've never even heard of if it wasn't
我什至从未听说过
for the fact that some community members
因为有些社区成员
step forward and created a API binding
前进并创建API绑定
for it and we'll talk more about this
为此，我们将详细讨论
box in a minute it's gonna be kind of a
一分钟的盒子，有点像
key key part of my talk toward the end
关键的关键部分
here but to kind of explain kind of the
在这里，但为了解释那种
moving parts and how spring social works
活动部件以及春季社交活动的工作方式
we have this thing called connect
我们有一个叫做connect的东西
controller it's just a spring MVC
控制器，这只是一个Spring MVC
controller and what connect controller
控制器和连接控制器
does is it handles that OAuth dance and
是不是可以处理OAuth跳舞和
it does it kind of generically it knows
它一般都知道
about how to do OAuth one it knows how
关于如何执行OAuth，它知道如何
to about how to do OAuth 2 and which one
关于如何执行OAuth 2以及哪一个
it does kind of just depends on which
它确实只是取决于哪个
API by which provider you're working
您正在使用的提供商的API
with well connect controller well pretty
与良好的连接控制器很好
much as what I just said if you you it
就像我刚才说的那样
handles different types of requests for
处理不同类型的请求
slash Connect slash provider ID now that
现在使用斜线连接斜线提供程序ID
slash Connect is hard-coded currently I
目前，斜线连接是硬编码的
have in
有
my backlog a plan to maybe change it so
我的积压计划可能会改变它
that's configurable because when I when
这是可配置的，因为当我何时
social first appeared there was really
社交第一次出现是真的
no good way of making that canet connect
没有使甜菜连接的好方法
part of that URL configurable but there
该URL的一部分是可配置的，但在那里
are ways of accomplishing that now so
是实现目标的方法
it's it I have an item of my backlog to
是的，我有一个待办事项
make it where you can change that if you
使其在您可以更改的地方，如果您
don't like the word connect for some
不喜欢连接这个词
reason but it will redirect the user the
原因，但它将重定向用户
users browser to whatever API is
用户浏览器到任何API
authorization page let them log in let
授权页面让他们登录let
them authorize the application and it's
他们授权该应用程序，并且
gonna redirect it they'll redirect back
要重定向它，他们将重定向回
and connect controller is going to
并连接控制器将
handle that redirect pull the
处理重定向重定向
authorization code off assuming it's a
授权码假设是
lot to pull the camera what the word is
很多拉相机的意思是什么
now the verifier off if it so auth one
现在关闭验证程序，如果它对一个进行身份验证
and it'll extend the scenes it'll
它会扩展场景
exchange that for an access token and it
将其交换为访问令牌，然后将其
does this by knowing it knows how to do
通过知道它知道该怎么做来做到这一点
what it's going to do by looking up this
查找此内容将要做什么
connection factory so that provider ID
连接工厂，以便提供程序ID
that's part of the URL is is some key
URL的一部分是一些关键
that tells it we're dealing with Twitter
告诉我们我们正在处理Twitter
or we're dealing with Facebook or
或者我们正在与Facebook打交道或
LinkedIn and it's gonna use that to go
LinkedIn，它将用它去
find a connection factory that knows how
找到一个知道如何的连接工厂
to do though how to do that dance for
尽管该怎么做
connect controller so it's gonna if for
连接控制器，所以如果
example it's Twitter if you say connect
例如，如果您说连接，那就是Twitter
slash the next Twitter it's gonna say
削减下一个Twitter，它会说
let's go to a connection factory locator
我们去连接工厂定位器
give me a connection factory for Twitter
给我一个Twitter的连接工厂
and the connection factory itself knows
连接工厂本身知道
how to create connections it knows how
如何创建连接，它知道如何
to talk to Twitter it knows how to
与Twitter交谈，它知道如何
exchange codes for tokens or verifiers
交换令牌或验证者的代码
for tokens or whatever the case might be
代币或任何情况
it just knows how to do all of this
它只知道如何做所有这一切
stuff things that are specific to that
特定的东西
provider that connect controller can't
连接控制器的提供程序无法
possibly know on its own that's what the
可能自己知道那是什么
connection factory does it also works
连接工厂也可以
with another thing called a service
与另一种叫做服务的东西
provider to help with that too and we'll
提供者也可以提供帮助，我们将
talk more about that a little bit later
稍后再谈更多
too
太
once it once it's created a connection
一旦建立连接
it's got this connection after doing
做完后有这个连接
this we're set of redirects this dance
这是我们这套舞蹈的重定向
Connect connect controller hands off via
通过连接连接控制器的手
token and the connection details to a
令牌和到的连接详细信息
connection repository connection
连接存储库连接
repository stores it in your database
存储库将其存储在数据库中
wherever you whatever the implementation
无论您在哪里执行
of your connection repository is it's
您的连接存储库是
going to store it for long-term use
将其存储以供长期使用
because once you have that connection
因为一旦建立联系
you can keep using that token over and
您可以继续使用该令牌，并且
over and over again
一遍又一遍地
to make requests against the API until
根据API发出请求，直到
the token is either revoked or expired
令牌已撤销或已过期
now one thing before I go any further I
现在我要做的一件事是
do have to stress this point because
确实必须强调这一点，因为
some people don't get it the word
有些人不明白
connection evokes things like Java dot
连接唤起诸如Java点之类的东西
IO dot or whatever the file connections
IO点或任何文件连接
or or HTTP connections or something are
或HTTP连接或某些
streams or things like that
流或类似的东西
unlike those this is not something you
不像那些不是你
have to close I've had so many people
必须关闭，我有很多人
ask me it's amazing how many people ask
问我，有很多人问
me how do you close a connection and
我如何关闭连接，
there is no concept of closed there's
没有封闭的概念
the idea of deleting a connection go to
删除连接的想法转到
the repository and remove it it's not a
存储库并删除它不是
connection though where you you you open
通过您打开的位置进行连接
it up you start some work and you close
开始工作，然后关闭
it when you're done like you might do
完成后就可以做到
with with like an input stream it's not
与输入流一样，它不是
that kind of thing it's it's
那种东西是
representative of the the relationship
关系的代表
or the agreement that your application
或您的申请的协议
is made with a provider that's all it is
由提供者完成
it's just a representation of that and
这只是那个的代表
we persist it long-term somewhere in a
我们将其长期保存在某处
database let's say and then sure you can
先说数据库，然后确定您可以
delete it you don't have to close it
删除它，您不必关闭它
when you're done you it'll it'll be
当你完成后，它将是
there the next time you come around you
下次你来你身边
can still use it once you have all this
一旦拥有了所有这些，仍然可以使用它
stuff you have this connection from that
你从那里有这种联系的东西
connection you can ask for an API
您可以要求一个API连接
binding and what this API binding is is
绑定，此API绑定是什么
again just a set of operations that know
再次只是一组知道的操作
how to make the rest calls to the API
如何对API进行其余调用
and it knows how to do it and make sure
它知道如何做到并确保
that the authorization header is on
授权标头已打开
every single request now in the case of
现在，对于
OAuth 2 it's fairly simple the
OAuth 2相当简单
authorization header I can quote it to
授权标头我可以引用它
you except for the token part I quoted
除了我引用的令牌部分
to you it's authorization is the the
对您来说，授权是
header name the value is bearer and the
标头名称，值是不记名，并且
value beyond bearer is the token name
承载以外的值是令牌名称
it's fairly simple in OAuth 2 in OAuth 1
在OAuth 1的OAuth 2中非常简单
it's a big pain in the butt I'm not I'm
我不是，我是一个巨大的屁股痛
going to try to tell you what it is
试图告诉你这是什么
there's a whole bunch of things that
有很多东西
goes into it
进入它
good news is you don't have to worry
好消息是您不必担心
about it you just make the call things
关于它，你只是打电话
work in every one of the cases at least
至少在每种情况下都可以工作
the ones I've implemented I've
我已经实现的那些
encouraged the community to do the same
鼓励社区也这样做
in every one of the API bindings I've
在我拥有的每个API绑定中
created I've also given you an out just
创造了我也给了你
in case something changes in the API not
万一API发生了变化
that a Facebook or Twitter ever changed
Facebook或Twitter曾经改变过
their API
他们的API
but if they did it gives you an out so
但是如果他们做到了，那么你会得到帮助
that if I don't have an a method it's
如果我没有方法，那就是
gonna give you what you want
会给你你想要的
I will also offer you a rest template
我还将为您提供休息模板
and it's just the same rest template
和其余的模板一样
that spring offers you already the
那春天已经给你了
difference though the small difference
差异虽然很小
is it's instrumented to know that every
是否知道每一个
single request you make will have that
您提出的单个请求将具有
authorization header in it so you don't
授权标头，因此您不必
still don't have to deal with tokens
仍然不必处理令牌
directly you still don't have to deal
直接你仍然不需要交易
with baking up an authorization header
与烘烤授权标头
I'll give you a rest template you make
我给你做一个休息模板
the call you want and I will make sure
您想要的电话，我会确保
that that authorization header is there
该授权标头在那里
for you so if you need to you can get
为您服务，因此如果您需要可以得到
that from the API binding so I'm gonna
来自API绑定的内容，所以我要
show you an example here in a minute
等一下给你看个例子
that looks a lot like this but here's
看起来很像这样，但这是
the general flow of the connect
连接的一般流程
controller so the first thing you can do
控制器，所以您可以做的第一件事
is do a get request for slash connect
是做一个斜线连接的获取请求
and what get the get request for / -
以及什么得到/-的获取请求
nick is going to do is it's gonna list
尼克要做的是列出
out all the providers that the
淘汰所有提供者
application is registered with
申请已向
essentially what this means is what are
本质上这意味着什么是
all the providers that we have a
我们拥有的所有提供商
connection factory for so if I have a
连接工厂，如果我有一个
connection factory for Twitter Facebook
Twitter Facebook的连接工厂
and LinkedIn they're going to show up
和LinkedIn他们将要出现
here and it's going to show me the
在这里，它将向我展示
status of those connections and give me
这些连接的状态，并给我
an opportunity perhaps to connect to
一个可能连接的机会
them now this Connect controller will
他们现在这个连接控制器将
handle this request but it's up to you
处理此请求，但这取决于您
to define what that view looks like I
定义那个视图看起来像我
don't know what your application is
不知道你的应用程序是什么
gonna look like I don't know what styles
看起来好像我不知道什么样式
you might want to put in there I'm just
你可能想放在那里，我只是
going to provide connections gonna
将提供连接
provide for you a model that you can use
为您提供可以使用的模型
to render your view to the user and then
将您的视图呈现给用户，然后
you can render that however you see fit
您可以渲染，但您认为合适
and that model is going to have things
那个模型将会有东西
in there like a list of providers and
在那儿像提供商列表
what the connection status is
连接状态是什么
essentially unless you say you wanted to
本质上除非你说你想
connect to one of these you connect to
连接到您连接的其中之一
Twitter so you click on that you're
Twitter，所以你点击你
gonna do it's going to end up with a get
要去做，最终会得到
request for / connect slash Twitter and
请求/连接斜线Twitter和
it's gonna show you yet another Status
它会告诉你另一个状态
page but it's very focused on Twitter
页面，但非常关注Twitter
and it's going to say you you haven't
会说你还没有
created any connections to Twitter yet
建立了与Twitter的任何连接
would you like to connect right now
您现在想连接吗
again this is just a view that that that
再次，这只是一个观点
you would have to provide Connect
您将必须提供Connect
controller gives you the model for that
控制器为您提供模型
but you have to provide the actual JSP
但是您必须提供实际的JSP
or timely for what
或及时的
template you like to use you're gonna
您想要使用的模板
have to provide that to render that to
必须提供它以将其呈现给
the user that said there is a feature in
说有功能的用户
the latest versions of spring social I
最新版本的Spring Social I
can't off the top of my head remember
不能离开我的头顶记住
the property name but it does come up in
属性名称，但确实出现在
an example later so I'll show it to you
一个例子，以后我会给你看
then there's a property you can set
然后有一个属性可以设置
where if you set it to true it will
如果将其设置为true，它将在哪里
automatically give you these views
自动为您提供这些视图
they're just not very pretty there times
他们在那里不是很漂亮
roman black text white background very
罗马黑文本白色背景非常
simple you're connected you're not
简单的连接就可以了
connected that kind of stuff
连接那种东西
extremely simple but it's just enough to
非常简单，但足以
kind of get you started until you're
可以让您开始，直到您
ready to actually start building your
准备实际开始构建您的
own views but that's an opt-in thing you
自己的观点，但这是您的选择
don't get that for free you have to set
不要免费获得，您必须设置
this property to topped into it so let's
将该属性置入顶部，所以让我们
just say you decide you want to connect
只是说您决定要连接
to Twitter so you click that connect
到Twitter，因此您单击该连接
with Twitter button and it's going to
与Twitter按钮，这将
post it's gonna redirect when you click
发布，当您单击时它将重定向
that button it's going to post a connect
该按钮将发布连接
slash Twitter which is going to trigger
削减将触发的Twitter
the connect controller to redirect to
连接控制器重定向到
Twitter and you what you're gonna see is
Twitter，您将看到的是
this authorize app you can get an
这个授权的应用程序，你可以得到一个
opportunity to authorize the application
授权申请的机会
now if you're not logged in to Twitter
现在，如果您尚未登录Twitter
the first thing you're gonna get to see
你会看到的第一件事
is a login page but once you're logged
是一个登录页面，但是一旦登录
in you get a chance to click that button
在你有机会点击那个按钮
and say yeah I'll authorize this app at
说是的，我将在以下位置授权此应用
which point it's going to redirect back
这将要重定向回
to get slash connect slash Twitter / o
得到斜线连接斜线Twitter / o
auth token equal whatever the the
auth令牌等于
request token was that's an OAuth 1
请求令牌是OAuth 1
thing and the verifier is whatever the
事物和验证者是什么
verifier was get an OAuth 1 thing that
验证者获得了一个OAuth 1，
you generally don't have to worry about
您通常不必担心
but this is something you might want to
但这是您可能想要的
know if you want to know how this works
知道你是否想知道它是如何工作的
into the covers well now that it's got
现在已经被掩盖了
this is this verifier it's going to
这是这个验证程序
exchange that behind-the-scenes for an
交换幕后花絮
access token it's going to take that
访问令牌，它将采取
token create a connection through the
令牌通过创建连接
connection factory it's going to save
连接工厂将要保存
that connection through the connection
通过连接的那个连接
repository and now that user who's
存储库，现在该用户
logged into this application and that
登录到该应用程序中
user who's logged into Twitter has now
登录Twitter的用户现在已经
created a connection between this
在这之间建立了联系
application and Twitter so that this
应用程序和Twitter，这样
application is able to see their data
应用程序能够看到他们的数据
and Twitter and so at this point now
和Twitter等，现在
when I go to slash connect slash Twitter
当我去斜线连接斜线Twitter
where before it says you're not
在说你不在之前
connected now it's telling me more stuff
现在连接，它告诉我更多东西
and it's telling me a little bit of
告诉我一些
general details about the user it
关于用户的一般细节
provides it provides in the in the model
提供模型中提供的
just some general
只是一些一般
information nothing specific but just
信息仅是具体信息
some common stuff that you might have in
您可能拥有的一些常见的东西
pretty much in any API you might want to
您可能想要在几乎所有API中使用
use such as an ID if there's a unique ID
如果有唯一ID，请使用ID等
such as their screen name sometimes they
例如他们的屏幕名称
don't have such a notion of a screen
没有屏幕的概念
name but if there is when it's there
名称，但是如果有的话
things like that now there's a few other
像现在这样的事情
things that spring solution will also
Spring 解决方案也将
offers I don't have pretty pictures for
提供我没有漂亮的照片
them but there at least in some ways
他们，但至少在某些方面
similar to that last set of slides
与最后一组幻灯片相似
there's provider sign-in controller and
有提供商登录控制器和
what provider signing controller does is
提供者签名控制器的作用是
it does a lot of the same stuff that
它做了很多相同的事情
connect controller does but it does it
连接控制器可以，但是可以
after it's done it doesn't create a
完成后不会创建一个
connection and it doesn't save it
连接，但不保存
through the connection repository
通过连接存储库
instead when it's finished with the
而是在完成后
OAuth dance it has information as a
OAuth舞蹈具有作为
token with that token it tries to get
令牌与它尝试获取
that general information about a user
有关用户的一般信息
and based on that user's ID on the on
并基于该用户的ID
the API it's talking to it'll compare
与之对话的API将进行比较
that with any existing connections in
与任何现有的连接
the repository and if it finds an
存储库，如果找到
existing connection in the repository
存储库中的现有连接
now it knows who the user is on that
现在它知道用户是谁
application and it will automatically
应用程序，它将自动
lock the user in this is not all that
锁定用户不是全部
different if you've seen it before this
如果您之前已经看过的话会有所不同
is not all that different from something
并没有什么不同
called Open ID Connect it's very similar
叫做Open ID Connect，它非常相似
in concept of how Open ID Connect works
关于Open ID Connect如何工作的概念
in fact that's on my that's another
事实上，那是我的，那是另一个
thing that's on my roadmap is to
我路线图上的事情是
actually give proper implementation of
实际给予适当的执行
Open ID Connect in here the difference
Open ID Connect在这里的区别
though is the flow that we go through
虽然我们经历的是
here where it differs from Open ID
这里与Open ID不同
Connect is open ID Connect it's very
连接是开放的ID连接非常
much a loft
很多阁楼
ooofff to provider sign and controller
ooofff到提供者标志和控制器
or work with any anything okay with even
或什至可以处理任何事情
OAuth one so you can use it with Twitter
OAuth One，因此您可以在Twitter上使用它
where you couldn't use Open ID connect
无法使用Open ID Connect的地方
with Twitter because their Twitter is
在Twitter上，因为他们的Twitter是
not a lot to I'm gonna address that a
我要解决的不是很多
little that point in a minute and
一分钟内一点点，
Twitter not being a lot - because I've
Twitter并不多-因为我
had a lot of questions about that before
之前对此有很多疑问
but give me a second
请给我一点
social authentication filter it
社会认证过滤器
essentially does the same thing as
本质上与
provider sign-in controller except it's
提供程序登录控制器，除了
a filter and more specifically it's an
一个过滤器，更具体地说是
implementation of springg Security's
实施Springg Security的
authentication filter why this is
身份验证过滤器这是为什么
important is it's just an authentication
重要的是，这只是身份验证
filter ignore the word social for a
过滤器忽略“社交”一词
moment it's just an authentication
只是一个认证
filter which means you can plug it in to
过滤器意味着您可以将其插入
spring Security's authentication
Spring Security 认证
I'm sorry spring securities filter chain
对不起，春季证券过滤链
and it plays just like any other
它像其他任何东西一样播放
authentication filter in spring
春季认证过滤器
securities filter chain would play
证券过滤器链将发挥作用
meaning that if you're using spring
表示如果您使用Spring
security in your application and you
应用程序和您的安全性
know as a spring developers we kind of
作为春季开发者，我们知道
hope you were if you're using spring
希望你在使用Spring
security you're gonna have all the
安全，您将拥有所有
benefits of spring security with that
Spring Security 的好处
things like to remember me things like I
喜欢想起我的事情
don't know John a blank right now what
现在不知道约翰空白
I'll cool things spring security does
我会为Spring Security 做些很棒的事情
ask rob windshield he'll know but it
问抢风挡，他会知道的，但是
basically it's just an authentication
基本上这只是一个认证
filter so the rule here is if you're
过滤，所以这里的规则是
using spring security in your
在您的系统中使用Spring Security
application you don't want to use
您不想使用的应用程序
provider signing controller you can it
提供者签名控制器就可以了
is possible it's just that there's gonna
可能只是因为
be a slight disconnect between the two
两者之间略有脱节
you're not going to get the full power
你不会获得全部权力
of spring security when you're using
使用时的Spring 安全性
provider signing controller you're going
您要去的提供商签名控制器
to want to use some of your
想用你的一些
authentication filter because it just
身份验证过滤器，因为它只是
naturally fits into the flow that's that
自然地适合这样的流程
spring security already offers but if
Spring Security 已经提供，但如果
you're using some other security
您正在使用其他安全性
mechanism you're not using spring
你不使用Spring 的机制
security you've rolled your own or
安全性，您已经自己动手或
you've got some other open source or
您还有其他一些开源或
maybe commercial project that's
也许是商业项目
implementing the security for your
为您实施安全
application that's where you're gonna
您要去的应用程序
want to use provider sign and controller
想要使用提供者标志和控制器
because it'll integrate with those other
因为它将与其他
things in it you have to do a little
里面的东西你需要做一点
overriding and of a couple of beans to
覆盖和几个 bean
kind of tell it how to integrate with
告诉它如何与
your your security mechanism but for the
您的安全机制，但对于
most part it just knows how to do that
大多数情况下，它只知道该怎么做
now I said real quick I need to address
现在我说我需要快速解决
this little office off topic on the sly
狡猾的这个小办公室的话题
but I said the Twitter is not a lot to
但是我说推特没有很多
the truth is it half is and I've had
事实是一半了，我已经
people on multiple occasions come to me
人们多次来找我
say hey why are you still using OAuth
说嘿，您为什么仍在使用OAuth
one when Twitter use supports OAuth 2
Twitter使用时支持OAuth 2
and the answer is Twitter supports OAuth
答案是Twitter支持OAuth
1 for their user facing api's they
1面向面向API的用户
support OAuth 2 for their client
支持其客户端的OAuth 2
credentials when you're using client
使用客户端时的凭据
type operations so if you're doing a
键入操作，以便在执行操作时
search on Twitter you can use either o
在Twitter上搜索，您可以使用
of 1 or auth to you either searching on
的1或对您进行身份验证
behalf of a user or you're searching on
代表用户或您正在搜索
behalf of an app so you have your choice
代表应用程式，让您自行选择
if you use if you're actually wanting to
如果您确实要使用
tweet on behalf of somebody you're still
代表您仍在鸣叫
using OAuth 1 they don't yet offer OAuth
使用OAuth 1他们还没有提供OAuth
2 is an option there so that's why I
2是一个选项，所以这就是为什么我
mentioned that all right
提到没事
there's a few other miscellaneous things
还有其他一些杂项
that have been added over the years
这些年来增加的
reconnect filter just the filter what
重新连接过滤器只是过滤器什么
reconnect filter knows how to do is if
重新连接过滤器知道该怎么办
by chance you make a call to one of
碰巧您打给其中一个
these operations in the API and it fails
API中的这些操作，但操作失败
and the reason it fails is because the
它失败的原因是
connection is no good either the
连接也不好
connection has expired the connection
连接已过期连接
has been revoked by the user for
已被用户吊销，用于
whatever reason that connection is no
无论什么原因，连接都没有
good anymore if that happens an
好了，如果那发生了
exception gets thrown and reconnect
引发异常并重新连接
filter knows how to deal with those
过滤器知道如何处理
kinds of exceptions and the way it deals
各种异常及其处理方式
with them is it walks you back through
和他们一起走过你
the authorization flow again and
授权流程再次出现，
attempts to grow to get a new connection
尝试成长以获得新的联系
that's so you don't have to worry about
这样您就不必担心
it and in fact this is this is different
它，实际上这是不同的
than how oh oh off to the spec Oh F 2
比规格还差哦哦F 2
recommends you do things Oh off to the
建议你做点事哦，去了
spec issues a refresh token along with
规范发布刷新令牌以及
an access token and so when the access
访问令牌，因此当访问
token expires you can take that refresh
令牌到期，您可以进行刷新
token and simply exchange it give new
令牌并简单交换即可获得新
access token and keep on going that's
访问令牌并继续进行
how the spec implements it that's not
规范如何实现它不是
how Facebook implements it nor is I
Facebook如何实现它，我也不是
believe that's how LinkedIn implements
相信这就是LinkedIn实施的方式
it
它
I know Facebook does not and the way
我知道Facebook并没有
Facebook implements it is they don't
Facebook实现了他们不这样做
give you a refresh token instead when
为您提供刷新令牌
your token expires they expect you to go
您的令牌到期，他们希望您离开
through the authorization flow again
再次通过授权流程
they do give you the opportunity they
他们确实给你机会，他们
give you something kind of like a
给你某种像
refresh token that anytime before your
在您之前的任何时间刷新令牌
token expires they have this notion of a
令牌过期，他们有一个
short lift token on a long lift okay
在长距离升降机上短提升令牌好吗
it's very confusing they give you the
他们给你的感觉很混乱
option of exchanging your access token
交换访问令牌的选项
for a longer you know your short lived
更长的时间，你知道你的短命
access token for a long lived access
长期访问的访问令牌
token but once your long lived access
令牌，但是一旦您长期访问
token expires you're out of luck you do
令牌过期，您不走运
have to go turn around and exchange that
必须转身交换
hour turn around and go through the
小时转身经过
authorization flow again and the reason
再次授权流程及其原因
it took me a long time to figure out why
我花了很长时间才弄清楚为什么
they would do that why did they break
他们会这样做，为什么他们会打破
the spec and their answer I finally came
规格和他们的答案，我终于来了
up with without asking anybody I just
不问我刚才的任何人
thought this up a after a great deal of
想了很多
stress is Facebook's way of doing is
压力是Facebook的工作方式
actually more secure because the the
实际上更安全，因为
spec gives the client an access token
spec为客户端提供访问令牌
and a refresh token and now the client
和刷新令牌，现在是客户端
the user can never come never has to
用户永远不会来，永远不必
come back to the application
回到应用程序
as long as that that application can
只要那个应用程序可以
keep exchanging refresh tokens for new
不断交换新的刷新令牌
access tokens that that application has
访问该应用程序具有的令牌
access to that users data forever unless
永久访问该用户的数据，除非
the user explicitly takes action to
用户明确采取行动
revoke that token to revoke that
撤消该令牌以撤消该令牌
authorization the application can now do
授权应用程序现在可以执行
whatever they want forever but with the
他们永远想要的东西，但是有了
way that Facebook does it the way that
Facebook做到的方式
some others do it if you have to go
其他一些人则必须这样做
through the authorization flow again
再次通过授权流程
that means the user has to be at the
这意味着用户必须在
application in the browser they have to
在浏览器中的应用程序，他们必须
at least keep using the application in
至少继续在
order for the application to continue
为了继续申请
having access to the API so it's it's
可以访问API，就是这样
not it's slightly passive in the sense
在某种意义上说它是被动的
that the user doesn't necessarily have
用户不一定拥有
to click that authorize button again as
以再次单击该授权按钮
long as the authorization is still good
只要授权还好
you'll just get issued a new token and
您将获得一个新的令牌，并且
the user will never even know that that
用户甚至不会知道
happened but the user does still have to
发生了，但用户仍然必须
keep using the application the user
继续使用用户的应用程序
can't walk away from the application and
无法离开应用程序，并且
the application have access to their
该应用程序可以访问他们的
data forever all right so that's what
数据永远都好，那就是
reconnect filter does there's also
重新连接过滤器也有
disconnect filter when a user does go to
用户确实要转到时断开过滤器
Facebook and does say I don't want this
Facebook，并说我不要这个
to be around anymore and they do revoke
到处走走，他们确实撤销了
that authorization Facebook has the
该授权Facebook具有
opportunity has the option of sending
机会可以选择发送
you a call back and telling you hey this
你回电告诉你嘿
users revoke the authorization you can
用户可以撤销授权
clean out any data you have for them if
清除您拥有的所有数据，如果
you want to and that's what disconnect
你想要的，那就是断开连接的原因
filter does and it only works for
过滤器确实起作用，并且仅适用于
Facebook currently at the moment I only
目前我只有Facebook
know that Facebook doing this one thing
知道Facebook正在做这件事
of I've kept in the back of my mind is
我一直在脑海里
if I find out about another API out
如果我发现另一个API
there that does a similar thing I might
那里做类似的事情我可能
make this more general and support it
使它更通用并支持它
more generally but right now it's
更普遍的是，现在
Facebook only there's a question over
Facebook只有一个问题
here somewhere
在某处
yeah generally what happens is the user
是的，通常情况是用户
would go so the question is is it I
会去，所以问题是我
think I'm getting your question right
认为我的问题是对的
how how would this get revoked is it
怎么会被撤销呢
through the API or is it through other
通过API还是通过其他
means the spec doesn't technically
意味着该规范在技术上不是
support it I mean it does sort of but it
支持它，我的意思是确实可以，但是
doesn't speak to it directly it's more
不直接跟它说话
like the user goes into Facebook or goes
就像用户进入Facebook或
into Twitter and says I don't trust this
推特上说我不相信这个
app anymore or I just simply don't want
应用了，或者我只是不想
them to have access anymore
他们可以访问了
whatever the reasons they are they go
不管他们是什么原因
into that they login they go to their
他们登录到他们去
like in Facebook if they go to the
就像在Facebook上，如果他们去
applications page my applications page
应用程序页面我的应用程序页面
and they find that app and they say yeah
他们找到了该应用，然后说
remove this one and yeah I mean there's
删除这个，是的，我的意思是
a couple of things there's a there's a
几件事情有一个
number of reasons why the token would no
代币拒绝的原因数量
longer be any good it's either expired
不再是好东西，要么过期
the authorization is gonna revoked
授权将被撤销
explicitly by the user there's a number
用户明确地有一个数字
of things that could go wrong the token
可能出错的事物
could just go bad you know there's a lot
可能会变坏，你知道有很多
of things that could happen and so if
可能发生的事情，如果
for any reason the reason we can't
出于任何原因，我们无法
access the API is because the token is
访问API是因为令牌是
no good there's a very specific set of
不好，有一套非常具体的
exceptions that get thrown that we
我们抛出的异常
understand that the tokens bad and if
了解令牌不好，如果
any of those tokens the token bad
这些令牌中的任何一个都不好
exceptions has happened and that's where
例外发生了，那就是
the reconnect filter kicks in and takes
重新连接过滤器启动并占用
takes over and tries to re-establish a
接管并尝试重新建立
new connection in the case of Facebook
Facebook的新连接
if they did revoke it if they didn't
如果他们没有撤消它
revoke any but the token expired then
撤销但令牌已过期的任何令牌
what's gonna happen is gonna do the
将会发生的是
redirect the authorizations still good
重定向授权仍然很好
even though the tokens bad the
即使代币不好
authorization is still good it'll
授权还是不错的
immediately redirect back the user will
立即重定向回用户
never know anything happen unless they
除非他们不知道会发生任何事情
pay really close attention to the
非常注意
address bar while it's flickering if
闪烁时的地址栏
they revoked it now the authorization is
他们现在撤销了授权
bad we redirect them back to Facebook
不好，我们将他们重定向回Facebook
now they have to authorize again there's
现在他们必须再次授权
a real-time update controller Facebook
实时更新控制器Facebook
has this weird way of doing real-time
有这种奇怪的实时方式
updates it comes down to a set of
更新它归结为一组
callbacks you have to go register your
您必须去注册的回调
act within your application setup you
在您的应用程序设置中行动
have to go register them with a URL that
必须去注册一个URL
they can send you real-time updates and
他们可以向您发送实时更新，
degrees limited on what you get back I
学位取决于你回来的我
don't spend a lot of time talking
不要花很多时间说话
this yet because at Facebook he actually
这是因为他在Facebook上实际上
keeps changing it on me laughs I tried
不断改变它，我一直在笑
it this still worked but it was still
它仍然有效，但仍然
the more recently Facebook has given you
Facebook最近给你的
a little bit more information than they
比他们多一些信息
used to essentially they just you
习惯上基本上他们只是你
register this this this URL with
用这个URL注册这个
Facebook and say this is where I want to
Facebook，说这是我想要的地方
receive real-time updates you tell them
收到您告诉他们的实时更新
what kind of real-time update you want
您想要什么样的实时更新
to get and they'll call you they'll
得到，他们会打电话给你，他们会
they'll send you a get regard not to get
他们会送你一个不要得到的关注
request a post request every so often
经常要求发帖
with any updates last I checked I did
我最近检查过的所有更新
they may have changed this but last I
他们可能已经改变了这一点，但最后我
checked the the update you got weren't
检查了您没有的更新
very useful on their own they were
他们自己非常有用
primarily an object ID so if a user
主要是对象ID，因此如果用户
changed some information about
更改了有关的一些信息
themselves that's it's a real-time
本身就是实时的
update if they change their email
如果他们更改电子邮件，则更新
address let's say and you were
地址说，你是
authorized to see their email address
被授权查看其电子邮件地址
you might get a real-time update for
您可能会获得有关的实时更新
that user but the the update you get is
该用户，但您得到的更新是
not going to tell you their email
不会告诉你他们的电子邮件
changed and here's here's their new
改变了，这是他们的新事物
email that's not what it's gonna tell
这不是要告诉的电子邮件
you it's just gonna say hey this user
你只会说嘿这个用户
changed go figure out figure it out for
改变去找出来解决
yourself just know that here's the user
你自己就知道这是用户
that change you go figure out what
那改变你去找出什么
changed and and update your records
更改并更新您的记录
accordingly
相应地
there's also generic OAuth 1 connection
还有通用的OAuth 1连接
factory in generic OAuth 2 connection
通用OAuth 2连接中的工厂
factory remember I spoke about these
工厂记得我讲过这些
connection factories earlier and
连接工厂更早和
everybody has one faith there's a
每个人都有一个信念
facebook connection factory a twitter
Facebook的连接工厂的Twitter
connection factory a LinkedIn connection
连接工厂LinkedIn连接
factory and every one of those implement
工厂和其中的每一个工具
either OAuth one connection factory or
OAuth一个连接工厂或
oh ah - connection factory there's these
哦-连接工厂有这些
generic ones these are kind of important
通用的这些很重要
I want to talk more about these toward
我想更多地谈论这些
the end of the time these are kind of
在时间的尽头，这些都是
important for api's that don't exist yet
对于尚不存在的api很重要
for API bindings that nobody has created
用于没有人创建的API绑定
yet so if I brand-new API comes up
但是如果我出现了全新的API
tomorrow let's just say we bring this
明天就说我们带这个
brand new social network called my peeps
全新的社交网络称为我的偷窥
online tomorrow and we want spring
明天在线，我们要春天
social support for my beeps right away
社会支持我的哔哔声
well you could spend the time creating
好吧，你可以花时间创建
all the stuff necessary to make this
所有必要的东西来做到这一点
this API work with spring social but
这个API与spring social一起工作，但是
you're gonna have to you've got to do a
你将不得不做一个
little bit of work to get it turned up
一点点工作来解决它
right now you can use generic both one
现在您可以同时使用通用
or generic OAuth 2 connection factory
或通用OAuth 2连接工厂
you configure one of these you
您配置其中之一
essentially tell it where the
本质上告诉它在哪里
authorization URL is where the token URL
授权URL是令牌URL所在的位置
is you tell it where what your your
你告诉它你在哪里吗
your applications credentials are for
您的应用程序凭证用于
that you configure these things for one
您将这些东西配置为一个
of these connection factories and what
这些连接工厂以及什么
it's going to do is it's going to
这将是要做的
register that as a connection factory
将其注册为连接工厂
within spring social and then when it
在春季社交活动中，然后何时
gives you it's gonna work just like it
给你它会像它一样工作
does for anybody else the difference is
对其他人而言，不同之处在于
when it gives you an API binding it's
当它为您提供API绑定时，
going to give you a rest template it's
给你一个休息模板
not going to give you some specific API
不会给你一些特定的API
binding like we get what we give you a
像我们得到给您的东西一样具有约束力
Facebook or Twitter it's just going to
Facebook或Twitter，这只是去
give you a rest template and that rest
给你一个休息模板，休息
templates gonna be instrumented to be
模板将被检测为
able to make sure the authorization
能够确保授权
headers on every request it's just like
每个请求的标题就像
the the you know worst case scenario the
你知道最坏的情况
simplest thing we could possibly give
我们可能会给的最简单的东西
you if we don't know anything else about
你，如果我们什么都不知道
the API and I'm gonna talk a little bit
API，我要谈一点
more about this later because I have
稍后再详细介绍，因为我有
some plans for what I want to do with
一些我想做的计划
this going forward and you might also
这向前发展，您可能还
want to know about I mentioned it
想知道我提到过
previously there is a lot one template a
以前有很多模板
lot - template if you want to work with
很多-如果您想使用的模板
OAuth directly you don't want to deal
您不想交易的OAuth直接
with the connect controller for whatever
与连接控制器进行任何操作
reason maybe you want to you want to
原因也许你想要你想要
build some of this stuff in but you
建立一些东西，但是你
don't want to use spring MVC I don't
不想使用spring MVC我不想
know why you would not want to do that I
知道为什么你不想那样做我
mean we're at a spring conference right
就是说我们在春季会议上
but maybe you don't want to use spring
但是也许你不想用spring
MVC you want to you do it through some
您想通过一些MVC实现它
other means you can work with OAuth 1
其他意味着您可以使用OAuth 1
template and walk to template directly
模板并直接转到模板
if you've seen any of the other ooofff
如果您看过其他ooofff
libraries out there there's several of
图书馆那里有几个
them they offer essentially what a lot
他们提供了很多东西
one an OAuth 2 template offer that's
一个OAuth 2模板提供的
what they offer out-of-the-box we offer
他们提供的开箱即用的产品
on top of that the connection that's
最重要的是
kind of the different differentiation
种不同的分化
between spring social and other
在春季社交和其他
libraries out there we offer offer what
我们提供的图书馆提供什么
they offer but we also offer this
他们提供，但我们也提供
connection flow on top of all that but
除了所有这些之外的连接流
where you might want to use these as if
您可能想在其中使用它们的地方
you're wanting to get client tokens
您想获取客户令牌
there is no such thing as a flow for a
没有这样的事情
client token or password grants if
客户令牌或密码授予，如果
you're doing a password grant where
您正在执行密码授予
you're given the users credentials and
您将获得用户凭证，
you just want to exchange that for a
你只想换一个
token there's no flow there there's no
令牌没有流就没有
redirect involved the simplest thing you
重定向涉及到最简单的事情
can do is here here's some credentials
可以做的是这里的一些凭证
give me a token back and so in those
给我一个令牌，在那些
cake cases that's where Olaf one oauth2
蛋糕盒，那是奥拉夫一个oauth2
template come in handy generally
模板通常派上用场
speaking though you probably don't want
说话虽然你可能不想
to mess with these guys but they're
惹这些家伙，但他们
there in case you want them so let me
如果你想要他们，那就让我
show you a couple of quick examples you
给你看几个简单的例子
may have seen some of these
可能已经看到其中一些
before that's okay we'll show them again
在那之前没关系，我们将再次展示给他们
I was actually I spend a little time
我实际上是花了一点时间
last night
昨晚
and I just gave up and reverted
我只是放弃并还原
everything because it was it was late
一切都是因为太晚了
and I was tired and it wasn't working
我很累，没有用
out my way I was hoping to actually skin
我本来希望我能皮肤
this differently so it looked more like
这不同，所以看起来更像
the spring one look and feel with all
春天的外观和感觉
the blues and all that stuff I just gave
布鲁斯和我刚给的所有东西
up it's just it wasn't worth it here we
只是在这里我们不值得
have spring social stroke case you can
有春季社交中风案例，你可以
go get this out of a head of github
去把它从github的头
under github.com slash spring - project
在github.com下斜线spring-项目
slash spring social samples it's one of
大幅削减春季社交样本，这是其中之一
them in there this is specifically
他们在那里，这是专门
there's several different spring social
有几个不同的春季社交
showcase examples in there I'm gonna
展示在那里的例子
start weeding those out and getting rid
开始除草并除草
of a few of them because some of them
其中一些，因为其中一些
are just old and I don't care to
年纪大了，我不在乎
maintain them anymore this is the one
维护它们，这是一个
called spring social showcase boot it's
叫做Spring Social Show Boot
based on spring boot because you know
基于spring boot，因为你知道
that's how we do things now so if you've
这就是我们现在要做的事情，所以如果您
worked with if you've ever worked with
如果您曾经合作过
spring social prior you know to spring
你知道春天之前的春天社交
boot coming along you know that you had
靴子来了，你知道你有
to write a lot of configuration a lot of
写很多配置很多
XML configuration and even after we
XML配置，甚至在我们
added the the the config project under
在下面添加了config项目
the core you still had to write a little
您仍然需要写一点核心
bit of XML you still you're right a
一点XML，您仍然是对的
little bit Java config well this one I'm
Java配置好一点我
gonna show you the code for this one
会告诉你这个代码
it's gonna be pretty cool but I'll show
它会很酷，但我会展示
you what it does first you can kind of
你先做什么，你可以
see where all the code I show you comes
看看我向您展示的所有代码都在哪里
into play so I'm gonna go ahead and just
发挥作用，所以我要继续前进
sign in here as me oh I it's awesome I
以我的身份在这里登录哦，我太棒了
love it when things work in front of
当事情在前面发生时喜欢它
people that's great I'm not sure what
那些很棒的人我不确定
just happened there
刚发生在那
oh I think I know what happened I need
哦，我想我知道我需要什么
to refresh this page because my yeah
刷新此页面，因为我是
that token that little that that token
那令牌那一点令牌
that's on the page the spring security
那是Spring Security 性的页面
puts on there it timed out I need to
放在那儿，我需要超时
actually probably deal with that a
实际上可能处理一个
little bit better than just showing you
比仅仅展示给你好一点
an ugly error page all right so we're
一个丑陋的错误页面，所以我们
logged in now Here I am I'm logged in as
现在登录我在这里，我以
Craig I'm gonna go check my connections
克雷格，我要去检查我的联系
and you can see in the URL it's slash
您可以在网址中看到斜线
connect and it's showing me that that
连接，并向我表明
Status page for Twitter Facebook and
Twitter Facebook的状态页和
LinkedIn so I can either click here or I
领英，所以我可以单击这里或
can go over here either one's gonna take
可以过去这里
me to the same place and I can connect
我到同一个地方，我可以连接
with Twitter and while we're at it let's
与Twitter，而我们在它，让我们
go ahead and just do something cool I
继续做一些很酷的事
can do this let's post a tweet basically
可以做到这一点，让我们基本上发布一条推文
telling all my friends that I did
告诉我所有的朋友我做了
connect with spring social showcase so
与春季社交展示会建立联系，因此
I'm going to connect with Twitter
我要与Twitter联系
I'm gonna authorize the app it's gonna
我要授权的应用程序
redirect back and now I'm connected to
重定向回，现在我已连接到
Twitter and you know I have some other
Twitter，你知道我还有其他
things I can do the most notable thing I
我能做的最显着的事情
can do is I can look at my timeline and
我能做的就是看看时间表
actually I think if my guess is right it
其实我想如果我的猜测是对的
probably failed to post that update and
可能无法发布该更新，并且
the reason it failed it because I
之所以失败，是因为我
actually did this last night and Twitter
实际上昨晚做了这个，Twitter
doesn't like it when you post to tweets
当您发布推文时不喜欢它
in a row with the same text so I think
连续使用相同的文字，所以我认为
it failed but it failed nice and
它失败了，但是失败了，很好，
silently if I dig around here that was
如果我在这里闲逛，那是默默的
me I'm this was me tweeting where's the
我，我是这是我在推特上
there is I'm logged in as a Booma dev so
我以Booma开发人员身份登录
I'm not tweeting to the world that I did
我没有在推特上发推文
this but this is what I did last night
但这是我昨晚所做的
I've connected with Spring social
我已经与Spring社交建立联系
showcase so that's that's when I when I
展示，那就是当我当我
did this last night that's what I posted
我昨晚做了这件事
had I not done it last night it would
如果我昨晚没做的话
have done done it with a different date
用不同的日期完成了
on it when I just did it the user
在我刚完成操作时，用户
profile my first name is Michael don't
个人资料，我的名字是Michael do n't
tell anybody it's big secret but I my
告诉任何人这是个大秘密，但我
haboob laboum a dev account shows as my
haboob laboum开发人员帐户显示为我
name is Michael
名字叫迈克尔
so says hello Michael walls that guess
所以说迈克尔你好，墙猜
my Twitter ID my screen name if it knew
我的Twitter ID我的屏幕名称（如果知道）
any of these other things it would show
这些其他任何会显示的东西
them but it doesn't have that
他们，但没有
information so it didn't here's some of
信息，所以这里没有
my friends on Twitter I don't have too
我在Twitter上的朋友也没有
many friends on Twitter I'm not even
Twitter上有很多朋友，我什至没有
sure why red carpet refs as a friend on
确定为什么红地毯认为朋友是
Twitter I honestly don't even know what
老实说，Twitter我什至都不知道
that is but nonetheless this is my hub
那不过是我的枢纽
Ouma dev caocao I don't have too many
Ouma dev caocao我没有太多
friends there I also have like no
那里的朋友我也没有
followers because nobody knows about huh
追随者，因为没人知道
boom with dev and I don't encourage you
开发人员的繁荣，我不鼓励你
to follow me there there's not a lot of
跟着我，那里没有很多
interesting things happen there if you
如果你在那里发生有趣的事情
want to do cool maybe I'll make my next
想做酷，也许我下一个
time I do this demo more interesting but
这次我做这个演示更有趣，但是
you know you don't have to direct
你知道你不必指挥
messages well that's not working right
消息很好，不能正常工作
now because I don't have my application
现在因为我没有我的申请
it doesn't have the authorization to do
它无权执行
that I probably should handle that a
我可能应该处理一个
little bit more gracefully but and in a
有点优雅，但在
various trend some of which I clearly
各种趋势，其中一些我很清楚
don't understand but these are these are
不明白，但是这些是
trending right now and this is more of a
现在趋势，这更多的是
general what's between what's trending
一般趋势之间有什么
on Twitter right now kind of kind of
现在在Twitter上有点
page I always have to always worry a
页面，我总是要经常担心
little bit when I pull this up cuz I'm
一点点，当我把这个拉起来，因为我
not sure what's gonna be in there and
不知道那里会有什么
what who what might
什么可能
a offend someone but not my fault I
冒犯某人，但不是我的错
didn't write it
没有写
this is just what happening on Twitter
这就是Twitter上发生的事情
if you're offended bring it up with
如果您得罪了，请提出来
Twitter well yeah
Twitter好吧
same thing with Facebook I can go
用Facebook也可以
connect to Facebook I'm not gonna tell
连接到Facebook我不会告诉
all my Facebook friends about it but I
我所有的Facebook朋友都对此感兴趣，但我
could and now I'm connected I can see my
可以，现在我已连接，我可以看到我的
profile on Facebook
在Facebook上的个人资料
I got my facebook ID as well as my name
我得到了我的facebook ID以及我的名字
now Facebook recently I say recently
现在Facebook最近我说最近
it's been a little over a year or two
已经过了一两年了
years maybe they started giving
几年后，他们开始给予
everybody a unique ID based on the
每个人都基于
application so if my this is my ID for
申请，因此如果这是我的ID
spring social showcase but if you create
春季社交展示，但如果您创建
an application and I logged into it I
一个应用程序，我登录了
would have a different ID if that your
如果您的
ID is very unique to the application
ID对于应用程序来说非常独特
they have this other thing called the
他们有另一件事叫做
business application API that lets you
业务应用程序API，可让您
kind of coordinate those if you have
协调那些，如果你有
multiple applications under the same
同一应用程序下的多个应用程序
heading and you want to somehow get
前进，你想以某种方式得到
those linked together there is an API
那些链接在一起的有一个API
for basically associating different
基本上将不同
business or different application
业务或其他应用
specific IDs as one user but right now
作为一个用户使用特定的ID，但现在
this this is just what we're seeing is
这就是我们所看到的
my ping social showcase ID my full name
我的ping社交展示台ID我的全名
you can see my feed I don't even know
你可以看到我不知道的提要
what's on my feet so this I don't think
我的脚在干什么，所以我不认为
I write anything that's offensive there
我在那写任何令人反感的东西
but you know I got one of those bb-8
但是你知道我有一个bb-8
robots that was pretty cool and there's
机器人很酷，还有
this group called nuru that occasionally
这个小组偶尔叫努鲁
sponsors some of these conferences you
赞助一些您的会议
should check them out they they have a
应该检查他们，他们有一个
great video that's Billy Williams he's
很棒的视频，他是比利·威廉姆斯
the most hilarious person I've ever met
我见过的最搞笑的人
personally you gotta check that out
你个人要检查一下
there's my friends I don't have any
有我的朋友，我什么都没有
Facebook friends actually I have plenty
Facebook朋友其实我有很多
I have lots I'm not that lonely but uh
我有很多我并不孤单，但是
at least my wife has my friend on
至少我妻子有我的朋友
Facebook but it doesn't show up here and
Facebook，但没有显示在这里，
the reason I've been showing you this is
我一直向你展示这个的原因是
because in in recent API changes that
因为在最近的API更改中
happen in Facebook when you ask for a
当您要求
set of friends you don't get everybody
一群没有你的朋友
you only get a list of friends who are
你只会得到一个名单的朋友
also using that same application that's
也使用相同的应用程序
an interesting restriction they placed
他们提出了一个有趣的限制
on it here a while back so even though I
就在这里，虽然我
have like 200 or something friends on
有200个左右的朋友
Facebook I have zero as far as this
Facebook我到目前为止的零
application is concerned because none of
涉及到应用程序，因为没有
my friends on Facebook have used spring
我在Facebook上的朋友都用过春季
social showcase which is not shocking at
社会展示，这并不令人震惊
all because my mom doesn't even have a
都是因为我妈妈甚至没有
what I do so they're not she's not gonna
我要做的是他们不是她不会
be able to to do this she will never
能够做到这一点，她永远不会
show up there
出现在那
of course I have my albums show you my
我当然有我的专辑给你看
truck so you can see the photos and
卡车，所以你可以看到照片和
everything I'll show you the cool
我会告诉你的一切很酷
version of my truck while we're talking
我们聊天时的卡车版本
about it so anyway there's you can
关于它，无论如何有你可以
access all this stuff that's happening
访问所有正在发生的事情
in Twitter and Facebook and I could do
在Twitter和Facebook上，我可以
it with LinkedIn but I'm not going to
它与LinkedIn，但我不会
these little links here in case
这些小链接，以防万一
anybody's wondering what simmer evoked
任何人都想知道什么引起了沸腾
is and SIM expired are there links I put
是，SIM卡过期了吗？
in there to simulate a token expiring or
在其中模拟令牌到期或
a token being revoked so I could test it
令牌被吊销，因此我可以对其进行测试
without actually having to go out to the
不必去外面
API and revoke it I'm not gonna bother
API并撤销它，我不会打扰
showing you those right now because
向您展示那些，因为
they're actually broken right now
他们现在真的坏了
because of some testing I've been doing
因为我一直在做一些测试
but there's all sorts of API calls you
但是有各种各样的API调用
can make this is only represents maybe
可以使这仅仅是代表也许
like 2% of what you can do with each of
就像您可以使用的每项功能的2％
these but I am gonna show you those I
这些，但我要告诉你那些我
can sign out now now I'm signed out of
我可以退出了，现在可以退出了
spring social showcase if I were to
春天的社会展示，如果我要
login as Roy you're gonna see he doesn't
以Roy身份登录，您会发现他没有
have any of those connections because
有任何联系，因为
it's a different user I would not like
这是我不想要的其他用户
Roy to log in and be able to tweet or
罗伊（Roy）登录并能够发布或
see my friends and or whatever that's
见我的朋友或其他
that's that's part of the security the
那就是安全的一部分
connection is associated with the user
连接与用户相关联
who's logged in but I could log in as a
谁已登录，但我可以以
boomin you can see now I have all these
你现在可以看到我拥有所有这些
connections they're still there what I
连接他们仍然在那里我
can also do is because I have created a
还能做的是因为我创建了一个
connection previously with Twitter I can
以前可以与Twitter建立连接
just say sign in with Twitter it goes to
只是说使用Twitter登录
Twitter and then redirects back and look
Twitter，然后重定向回去并查看
I'm signed in again what it did is it
我再次登录是什么
figured out oh I did that OAuth dance I
知道哦，我参加了OAuth舞蹈
looked up your user information I
查找了您的用户信息我
compared your user ID with a user ID I
比较了您的用户ID和用户ID I
have on record for a connection based on
根据以下记录进行连接
that connection I know who the user is
该连接我知道用户是谁
so I'll go ahead and log that user in
所以我将继续登录该用户
you can do the same thing at Facebook it
你可以在Facebook上做同样的事情
would also work with LinkedIn if I did
如果我这样做，也可以与LinkedIn合作
the same thing with LinkedIn nice thing
与LinkedIn一样的好东西
about Facebook is they don't actually
关于Facebook是他们实际上不是
show you that little landing page for a
给你看那个登陆页面
moment before they come back they come
他们回来之前的时刻
back immediately I should point this out
马上回来，我应该指出这一点
some people ask what's this
有人问这是什么
that's something Facebook does I have no
那是Facebook我没有的东西
idea why they do it it doesn't hurt
知道他们为什么这样做并没有伤害
anything don't worry yourself with it
什么都不用担心
but a lot of people will ask what that
但是很多人会问
is
是
I think my codes broke they say why is
我认为我的密码坏了，他们说为什么
spring social putting that in the URL
Spring Social将其放入URL
it's not it's Facebook doing it I don't
不是不是Facebook在做，我不是
know why they do that all right so I
知道为什么他们会这样做，所以我
think I'm showing you about everything I
想我正在向你展示我的一切
can show you with this except for the
可以向您展示，除了
LinkedIn stuff which is at this point
此时的LinkedIn内容
kind of boring cuz it's not much
有点无聊，因为不多
different than what you'd do with a
与您将要执行的操作不同
Facebook and Twitter so what I'm gonna
Facebook和Twitter，我该怎么办
show you another example actually I
告诉你另一个例子我
won't show you the code for this one
不会向您显示此代码
first this is a little exciting here's
首先，这有点令人兴奋
to spring social showcase boot there's a
春季社交展示靴，有一个
lot of stuff in here that's it's there
这里有很多东西
for the sole purpose of doing things of
做某事的唯一目的
Facebook so the controller once I have a
Facebook的，所以一旦我有一个控制器
connection I have this like Facebook
连接我有这个像Facebook
friends controller that's injected who
注入谁的朋友控制器
serve and get this ring see it better
服务并得到这枚戒指更好看
that's injected with a Facebook object
注入了Facebook对象
Facebook is the kind of root of the API
Facebook是API的根源
binding and from that Facebook object I
绑定，并从那个Facebook对象开始
do things like Facebook friend
做类似Facebook的朋友
operations get friend profiles and it
操作获取朋友个人资料，并且
puts that into the model but I at no
将其放入模型中，但我没有
point that I do a get request for graph
指向我获取图表请求
that I could craft that facebook.com
我可以制作那个facebook.com
slash whatever my ID is slash friends I
砍掉我的身份证就是我的朋友
didn't do that this is all happening
没有做到这一切
under the covers I didn't have to put
在我不需要放的掩护下
the authorization header in there I
我那里的授权标头
didn't have to do anything I just call
不必做我刚刚打电话的任何事情
the method I get it what I want out of
我想要的方法
it and there's a most of this code in
它，其中大部分代码
here is doing that kind of thing so I'm
这里正在做这种事情，所以我
not gonna show you all of that but I
不会告诉你所有的一切，但我
will show you is the configuration for
将显示您的配置
this I'll show you the security
我会告诉你安全性
configuration which is not terribly
配置不是很糟糕
exciting unless unless this was a spring
除非这是春天，否则令人兴奋
security talk but it's fairly basic
安全性讨论，但这很基本
spring security configuration setting up
Spring Security 配置设置
some JDBC authentication so I can
一些JDBC身份验证，这样我就可以
authenticate against an account table
根据帐户表进行身份验证
I've got some stuff where I'm ignoring
我有一些我忽略的东西
certain paths I'm configuring the basic
我正在配置某些路径的基本
spring security stuff that which has
Spring Security 的东西，有
nothing to do is bring social but I'm
没什么可带来社交的，但是我
showing you that just so you can see
向您展示，以便您可以看到
that in fact there is stuff here
实际上这里有东西
happening with regard to spring so those
关于春天发生的事情
spring security here is just your basic
Spring Security 仅是您的基本要求
boot initializer if you've ever built a
引导初始化程序，如果您曾经构建过
spring boot app and you wanted to create
spring boot 应用程序，您想创建
a war file out of it when you're done
完成后从中取出战争文件
that's what this does you need one of
这就是您需要的其中之一
these I don't care if it Springs toast
这些我不在乎是否吐司
or not you're gonna need one of those so
还是你会需要这些之一
this is really just boilerplate code for
这真的只是样板代码
the most part and then there's the only
大部分，然后只有
other whoops
其他的呐喊
the only other configuration that you
您唯一的其他配置
have is application that Java which has
有的是Java拥有的应用程序
its main method it's the bootstrap class
它的主要方法是bootstrap类
for spring social and but there's
对于春季社交活动，但是有
nothing else
没有其他的
a lot of configuration enable
许多配置启用
configuration properties mately this is
配置属性，这是
the only thing that has anything at all
唯一一无所有的东西
to do with spring social is that being
与春季社交活动有关的是
right there and that's there because I'm
就在那里，因为我在
using provider sign-in controller and
使用提供商登录控制器和
provider sign-in controller does not
提供程序登录控制器没有
know what kind of security I'm using I
知道我正在使用哪种安全性
could use spring security I could use
可以使用我可以使用的spring security
other means but it's simply using the
其他方式，但只是使用
HTTP session request cache from spring
来自Spring的HTTP会话请求缓存
security to do its sign-in that's it and
进行登录的安全性就是这样
so I had to create one of these guys and
所以我不得不创建一个这些人，
registered as a beam but after that I'm
注册为光束，但之后我
done there is no spring social
做到没有春季社交
configuration anywhere in here from a
从这里的任何地方配置
spring perspective there is none because
春天的观点是没有的，因为
spring boot took care of it for me how
spring boot 帮我照顾它
did it take care of it for me
它为我照顾好了吗
I added spring socials I'm sorry spring
我添加了春季社交活动，对不起春天
boots face social Facebook what's the
靴子面对社交Facebook是什么
word I'm looking forward here
我在这里期待的词
starter I added the starter to my
我将启动器添加到了
dependent my build I added the starters
取决于我的构建，我添加了启动器
for Twitter to my build it took care of
推特到我的构建它照顾
it from there
从那里
let me show you the build just to kind
让我向您展示构建方式
of put put a fine point on what it is
的重点是什么
I'm saying here those first three
我说的是前三个
dependencies there or what make that
那里的依赖或造成的原因
work by virtue of the fact that I have
由于我有一个事实而工作
those dependencies in my build
我构建中的那些依赖
I have Auto configuration support for
我有自动配置支持
Twitter Facebook and LinkedIn and the
Twitter Facebook和LinkedIn，以及
only other thing I needed to tell it was
我只需要告诉其他事情是
my credentials for those api's so I had
我对那些api的凭据，所以我有
to go out to Facebook I had to go out to
去Facebook，我必须去
Twitter I'll just quickly show you what
Twitter我将快速向您展示
that looks like I can go to dev Twitter
看起来我可以去开发Twitter
comm I hope I'm like oh I'm logged in as
通讯，我希望我喜欢哦，我以
a boomba dev I'll do it too LinkedIn
我也要这么做
developer I can do I Facebook Facebook
开发人员我可以做到Facebook Facebook
will work I go to Facebook I can look at
会工作，我去Facebook，我可以看看
my apps I go to spring social showcase
我的应用程序我去春季社交展示
and you can see right here after I
我之后你可以在这里看到
registered with Facebook and answered
在Facebook注册并回答
some questions about my app they're
关于我的应用的一些问题
giving me an app ID and a secret that I
给我一个应用程序ID和一个秘密
can get if I were to ask them nicely but
可以得到我是否很好地问他们，但是
I get this app ID I get this app secret
我得到这个应用程序ID我得到这个应用程序的秘密
and then I have to tell Spring social
然后我必须告诉Spring social
about it
关于它
the way I tell spring social about it is
我告诉Spring Social的方式是
with the same way you would tell spring
用跟春天说的一样
boot applications about anything I said
关于我说的任何东西启动应用程序
it through a property either in my
通过我的财产
environment variables application that
环境变量的应用说明
yeah mole application that properties if
是的，摩尔特性是
this was a spring cloud-based project I
这是一个基于春季云的项目
might put it in the configuration server
可能将其放在配置服务器中
here you go here's my credentials for
在这里，你去这里是我的凭据
spring social Facebook Twitter and
春季社交Facebook Twitter和
LinkedIn please don't write those down
领英，请不要写下来
please don't take a photo of them I've
请不要给他们拍张照片
recently up until up until fairly
最近直到直到相当
recently I actually had those committed
最近我实际上有那些承诺
into github the thinking being is this
进入github的想法是
is just a demo app who cares there's two
只是一个演示应用程序，在乎两个
things that go wrong when that happens
发生这种情况时会出错
number one is I started getting weird
第一是我开始变得怪异
messages on Facebook and from I don't
消息在Facebook上，而我却没有
know how it's happening I couldn't
知道怎么回事我不能
figured it out but it's the only thing
想通了，但这是唯一的事情
I've come to concluded is that somehow
我得出的结论是
people were using my credentials my
人们正在使用我的凭据
application credentials to do something
应用程序凭证以执行某项操作
weird with my Facebook stuff and number
我的Facebook资料和号码很奇怪
two is Facebook and Twitter and LinkedIn
两个是Facebook，Twitter和LinkedIn
they start getting angry with me because
他们开始生我的气，因为
I've published these things publicly so
我已经公开发布了这些东西，所以
I've taken them out if you ever download
如果您下载了，我就把它们取出来了
spring social showcase out of github and
github之外的春季社交展示和
want to run it first thing I want to do
要运行它我想做的第一件事
is visit this file and go add those add
是访问此文件并去添加那些添加
your own keys in there yeah you had a
你自己的钥匙在那里
question
题
there is support for I think it's it I
有支持，我认为是我
think the current version is yeah you
认为当前版本是
saw 2.0 that's that was the version of
看到2.0就是那个版本
spring of the spring social Facebook
春季社交社交之春
that's not the version of Facebook's API
那不是Facebook API的版本
spring so I think spring social supports
春天，所以我认为春天的社会支持
2.3 currently force you into doing 2.4 I
2.3目前迫使您去做2.4 I
hate them for that by the way and the
为此而讨厌他们
problem is is that they're they're
问题是他们是他们
expecting that if you create an older if
期望如果您创建一个较旧的
you have an old application they're
你有一个旧的应用程序
gonna let you kind of be grandfathered
会让你有点祖父
into that if you have a new application
如果您有一个新的应用程序
there's no reason why you can't just
没有理由为什么你不能只是
immediately today start using the new
今天立即开始使用新的
API what they're not accounting for is
他们不考虑的API是
things like spring social wear when they
诸如春季社交服装之类的东西
drop a new release suddenly I have to
突然放弃一个新版本
implement that suddenly I have to do
意识到我突然要做
that and that's that's it's really hard
那就是那真的很难
for me to keep up with that so I think
我要跟上那个，所以我想
currently Spring socials 2.3 it's gonna
当前Spring socials 2.3
end up having support for 2.4 one of the
最终获得对2.4之一的支持
things I it's on my road map as well if
我在路线图上的事情以及
nothing else is to simply allow you to
没有别的，只是让你
set the version it'll default to
设置默认的版本
whatever I thought the right one would
无论我认为合适的人会
be but if you wanted to you could tell
是，但是如果你想告诉你
it a different version it won't change
它是一个不会改变的不同版本
the URL patterns it won't change the API
URL模式不会改变API
bindings in any other way it'll just
以任何其他方式绑定
change the URLs with the hope that it's
更改网址，希望它是
gonna work that's the best I can do
我会做的最好的事
immediately and then if you can wait a
立即，然后如果您可以等待
little bit then the next version will
一点点，那么下一个版本将
support 2.4 ideally it should work
支持2.4，它应该可以正常工作
ideally unless they really made some
除非他们真的做了一些
huge braking changes it would just
巨大的制动变化
simply changing the URL will work I
只需更改URL就可以了
I hate Facebook really I really do I
我真的很讨厌Facebook
hate them for that reason they're not
讨厌他们，因为他们不是
there I understand their reasoning
在那里我了解他们的理由
because they're but they're just not
因为他们是，但他们不是
thinking about API bindings that would
考虑API绑定
have to change like the day that this
必须像今天这样改变
new things released is it's really
新发布的东西是真的
annoying
烦人的
what they'll let you do it they'll let
他们会让你做什么，他们会让
old applications use new eight new URLs
旧应用程序使用新的八个新URL
but they won't let old application are
但他们不会让旧的应用程序成为
new applications usual old URLs yeah so
新应用程序通常使用旧网址，是的
not really
并不是的
we've we've chatted we've spent some
我们聊天，我们花了一些
time talking about it I don't think they
时间谈论它，我不认为他们
care I don't think they care enough they
在乎我认为他们不够在乎
don't we're just little compared to them
难道我们与他们相比只是很少
and the most that's happened is when I
最发生的是当我
had a conversation with them at one time
一次与他们交谈
about this I thought we were getting
关于这个，我以为我们越来越
somewhere and it finally just ended with
某个地方，它最终以
them sending to me an invitation to f8
他们向我发送了f8邀请
and so that that's really where it ended
所以那才是真正的结局
and I wish there was more I could do
我希望还有更多我可以做的
about it
关于它
I've tried I don't know I don't know
我已经试过了我不知道
what to do about it I wait I wish there
我该怎么办，我希望在那里
was more I could do but right now it's
我可以做的更多，但现在
just I have to keep playing catch-up
只是我必须继续追赶
we'll talk more about that later in a
我们将在稍后的内容中进一步讨论
minute - all right so before we move on
分钟-好的，所以在继续之前
I'm actually running a little short on
我实际上在
time but that's okay let me show you one
时间，但是没关系，让我向您展示
more example you may have seen this
更多示例，您可能已经看到了
before I don't know I've shown it a few
在我不知道我已经展示了一些之前
times everything I just showed you even
倍我刚才给你看的一切
though I showed you no really no real
虽然我没有告诉过你
spring social configuration in that code
该代码中的春季社交配置
that was still too much code I can still
那仍然是太多的代码，我仍然可以
do better than that I can still write
比我仍然可以写的更好
less code than that thanks to the spring
比春天少的代码
boot now that what I'm about to show you
现在就启动我要向您显示的内容
I'm going to preface it by saying this
我将以这样说作为开头
is not an application you're gonna go to
不是您要去的应用程序
work and tomorrow and you're gonna write
工作和明天，你要写
it and you're gonna show it to your boss
它，你会把它展示给你的老板
and they're gonna give you a pat on the
他们会给你一个拍拍
back and a promotion you're not gonna
回来，你不会升职
get that kind of thing from what I'm
从我身上得到那种东西
about to show you this is very much the
即将向您展示这非常
hello world app for spring social very
春季社交的你好世界应用程序非常
as much this is the least amount of code
这是最少的代码量
I can write and make spring social do
我可以写作并使春季成为社交活动
something interesting
有趣的事情
that's all it amounts to and if you if
这就是全部，如果您
you followed any of the spring boot
您跟随任何 spring boot
teams claims over the last few years
团队在过去几年中声称
it's always been fun for them to write
他们写东西总是很有趣
code that fits in less than 140
少于140的代码
characters so that they can tweet an
字符，以便他们可以发布
application it's been fun for them to do
应用程序对他们来说很有趣
and I thought if they're tweeting
我以为他们在发推文
applications here is the project leaf or
这里的应用程序是项目叶子或
spring social who's you know familiar
春季社交你认识谁
with Twitter I should be able to do the
使用Twitter，我应该能够
same kind of thing and so I know the
同样的事情，所以我知道
what I'm about to show you exists only
我要告诉你的只是存在
because I wanted to beat them at their
因为我想击败他们
at their game I wanted to have the
在他们的比赛中，我想拥有
smallest spring boot application that's
最小的Spring Boot应用程序
the only reason exist ideally if I had
如果我有的话，理想的唯一原因是存在
some time I'm getting really close to
一段时间我真的很接近
being able to write an application that
能够编写一个应用程序
can tweet itself really close but not
可以鸣叫自己真的很近，但不能
quite we're still a little ways from
相当我们还有一点距离
that let me run it for you first so I
让我先为你运行它，所以我
already have it in this directory so I'm
已经在此目录中，所以我
going to Spring Run it's a twitter app
去Spring Run这是一个Twitter应用程序
and of course it's in groovy using the
当然，使用
spring boots CLI there's a couple of
spring boot CLI有几个
points to be made while we're waiting
我们在等待时要提出的要点
for this to start up again you're not
为了这个再次启动，你不是
gonna use this application in production
将在生产中使用此应用程序
what I'm about to show you it's it's
我要告诉你的是
hardly production ready but it does
几乎没有生产准备，但确实
demonstrate the fact that again if
再次证明事实
you're building applications with spring
您正在使用Spring构建应用程序
boot and you want to use spring social I
启动，您想使用Spring Social I
have gone out of my way to make that as
已经竭尽全力使它成为
simple as I possibly can and I have more
尽可能简单，我有更多
in line in store that I'm planning to do
我打算在商店里排队
to make it even simpler if you if you
让它变得更简单，如果您
wait now this is awesome I love it when
现在等待，这太棒了，我喜欢
things go well during talks what are we
会谈中一切顺利我们是什么
seeing here Tomcat is Tomcat still
看到这里Tomcat仍然是Tomcat
running over here I thought I killed it
在这里跑来跑去我以为我杀了它
oh no guess I did not my bad that
哦，不，我没有我的坏
happens almost every time I get well it
几乎每次我康复时都会发生
oh yeah I'm not running it there I'm
哦，是的，我不在那儿运行
running it as a spring boot app so now
作为 spring boot 应用程序运行它，所以现在
now it should be dead like I said I love
现在应该死了，就像我说的我爱
it when things work well in talks so
谈判中一切顺利时，
we'll let this start up looks like it's
我们让这个启动看起来像是
gonna be a little bit healthier this
这样会更健康
time we're gonna go to the browser now
时间我们现在要去浏览器
again the this is not only the smallest
再次，这不仅是最小的
spring social app I've ever seen this is
我见过的春季社交应用程序是
the smallest spring boot app I've ever
我所见过的最小的Spring Boot应用程序
seen I just want to show you what it
看到我只是想告诉你它
does before I show you what the code
在我告诉你代码之前
looks like so I'm gonna connect to
看起来像这样，我要连接到
Twitter and it says you aren't connected
Twitter，并说您没有连接
to Twitter yet click the button to
到Twitter，然后单击按钮
connect to your Twitter account sure I
确保连接到您的Twitter帐户
will and it's gonna go there or you want
会，它会去那里，或者你想要
to authorize that sure and it's going to
授权的肯定，这将
come back and it says hello Michael
回来，它说你好迈克尔
walls you are now connected to Twitter
您现在已连接到Twitter的墙壁
as a Booma dev it tells me that I'm
作为Booma开发人员，它告诉我
connected it tells me what my full name
连接它告诉我我的全名
is it tells me what my screen name is so
它告诉我我的屏幕名称是什么
it's done something interesting
它做了一些有趣的事情
now how many lines of code do you think
现在您认为多少行代码
it took for me to write that a wild
我花了这么大的钱
guesses
猜测
got here five
到这里五
- you think - twos good okay
-你想-很好
well let's just see what that looks like
好吧，让我们看看它是什么样子
there we go that's it right there one
我们去那里就在那里
line of code I acknowledge that this is
代码行，我承认这是
not the most expressive code I've ever
不是我见过的最具表现力的代码
written that wasn't the point but that
写那不是重点，但那
works and now the one thing I didn't
工作，现在我没有的一件事
show you I this is I am being a little
告诉你我这是我有点
bit disingenuous here I did not show you
有点卑鄙，我没给你看
the application that properties file
属性文件的应用程序
which has these properties in it and the
其中具有这些属性以及
reason I didn't show you that is if you
我没有告诉你的原因是，如果你
want to count that go ahead it's four
想算一下继续前进的时间是四个
lines of code so what but if you want to
几行代码，但是如果您想
count it that's great but I don't count
算是很棒，但我不算
it the reason I don't count it is
这是我不计算的原因
because application out properties was
因为应用程序出属性是
just a convenient place to put that
只是一个方便的地方
stuff I could have just as easily have
我本来可以拥有的东西
put it in the environment variables and
把它放在环境变量中
it would have also worked and that I
它也将起作用，而我
wouldn't consider that lines of code I
不会考虑我的那几行代码
could have just as easily if this was a
如果这是一个
spring cloud app I could have just as
我可以拥有的春季云应用程序
easily put it in a centralized
轻松地将其集中
configuration server and I wouldn't
配置服务器，我不会
consider that lines of code I just as a
认为那行代码就像
convenience I put it in an application
方便，我把它放在一个应用程序中
up property so that's why I don't count
财产，所以这就是为什么我不算
these as lines of code do you have a
这些作为代码行，您有
question
题
hang on hang tight I'm gonna try to show
挂紧，我要尝试显示
you that before we get out of here
你在我们离开这里之前
something like that yes sure in the case
这样的事情肯定是这样
of a disc in the case of a desktop
如果是台式机，则为光盘
application you'd probably want to use
您可能想使用的应用程序
the password grant in which case you
密码授予在这种情况下，您
definitely want to use a lot to template
肯定要用很多模板
I don't have an example for that but I
我没有这个例子，但我
mean one is pretty straightforward
意思是很简单
because it's just a single method call
因为这只是一个方法调用
on a walk to template there's no
步行到模板时没有
redirect in the case of a password grant
在授予密码的情况下重定向
it's simply give me the traditionals
只是给我传统
I'll give you credentials you give me a
我给你凭证，你给我一个
password back there is no redirect in
密码返回没有重定向
that case and so for a mobile app for a
这种情况，对于移动应用
desktop app there's no redirect involved
桌面应用程序不涉及重定向
in fact that's where things become
事实就是这样
tricky on a mobile app you can redirect
您可以重定向的移动应用上的棘手问题
and you can redirect back into an app
您可以重定向回应用程序
we've done it it's it requires a little
我们已经做到了，这需要一些
setup but you can do it a desktop app I
设置，但您可以将其作为桌面应用
can read or I can open up a browser but
可以阅读，也可以打开浏览器，但是
I can't send you back into the app
我无法将您送回应用程式
yeah in those cases in the case of a
是的，在这些情况下，
desktop app or a mobile app or in some
桌面应用程序或移动应用程序或某些
other cases that's not that's where
其他情况并非如此
authorization code grant which is what
授权码授予是什么
connect controller handles best it's not
连接控制器可以很好地处理
appropriate you need to find any views
适合您需要找到任何视图
password grant or in the case of a
密码授予或
client application client grant those
客户端应用程序客户端授予那些
are the things that are more appropriate
是更合适的东西
so let me in both I know what a lot to
所以让我俩都知道
template will handle both of those so
模板将处理这两个问题
let's me move quickly cuz I got like
让我快速移动，因为我喜欢
very few moments left I was actually
剩下的片刻我实际上是
expecting to finish earlier today that
预计今天早些时候完成
never works out well for me
永远对我不好
so integrate integration spring
所以整合整合Spring
integration and Twitter this is a little
集成和Twitter这有点
chunk of code this is a really simple
这段代码非常简单
set of code that I've written and I'm
我编写的一组代码
going to show you it running here in a
会向您展示它在这里运行
minute hopefully it's still running it
分钟希望它还在运行
was running before I started this
在我开始之前就在运行
morning it's been running since the
自从
keynote on Tuesday night here's some
周二晚上的主题演讲，这里有一些
code that sets up a real basic Twitter
设置真正的基本Twitter的代码
source for spring integration and what
Spring 集成的来源以及什么
I'm telling it is given this Twitter
我告诉它这个Twitter
which is the root did the base of
这是根的基础
Twitter's API binding given this Twitter
Twitter的API绑定为此Twitter提供
object I want you to search and the prat
我要你搜索的对象和老鼠
and I want you to search for things that
我要你搜寻那些
that are either spring at spring 1/2 GX
在春天1/2 GX的春天
or hashtag s2 GX that's what I want you
或标签s2 GX就是我想要的
to search for and that's the message
搜索，这就是信息
source that's just a good old fashioned
只是一个老式的资源
spring integration message source and
Spring集成消息源和
I'm not using I'm not using spring
我不使用我不使用Spring
integrations XML configuration I'm using
我正在使用的集成XML配置
their Java config because I don't like
他们的Java配置，因为我不喜欢
to talk about XML these days but I'm
最近谈论XML，但是我
setting up this message source and once
设置此消息源，一次
I once I have this message source I can
一旦有了此消息源，我就可以
do things like set up this integration
做类似设置此集成的操作
flow we're given that that tweet source
流程，我们知道该推文来源
I'm going to poll every 10 seconds now
我现在每10秒轮询一次
the reason I picked 10 seconds 2 seconds
我选择10秒2秒的原因
is as small as I could reasonably do it
尽可能地小
and the reason is given a client
原因是客户
credentials grant on Twitter their rate
凭据在Twitter上授予其费率
limiting allows you to do a I came every
限制可以让你做到
way I have to do the math to figure it
我必须做数学来计算的方式
out but basically you can do something
出去，但基本上你可以做点什么
every two seconds you can search every 2
每两秒钟您可以每2秒钟搜索一次
seconds if you try to search more
秒，如果您尝试搜索更多
frequently than that it's going to give
经常比它会给
you a rate limited except
您限价，除了
and you're gonna get kicked out I
然后你会被踢出去
actually had this happen when I had two
当我有两个时，实际上发生了这种情况
instances of this running even though it
即使它正在运行的实例
was set at two seconds they had two
被设置为两秒钟他们有两个
instances running and they were both
实例正在运行，它们都
beating up on Twitter with the same
在Twitter上以同样的方式击败
application ID so I brought it back to
应用程序ID，所以我把它带回了
10 seconds cuz I figured that was
10秒因为我觉得那是
reasonable amount of time anyway and I
无论如何，合理的时间和我
also figured I could run multiple
还以为我可以跑多个
instances of this without it them
没有它的实例
getting in the way I could have run up
妨碍我本来可以跑起来
to five without them getting in the way
到五个，而不会妨碍他们
and then I'm expecting only up to ten
然后我期望最多只有十个
messages for poll and that's kind of you
进行民意测验的消息，这就是你
know that's that's tunable you want to
知道那是您想要的可调
get that tor it's a sweet spot but for
得到那个tor，这是一个好地方，但对于
the purposes of my application I set it
我设置应用程序的目的
to ten I'm gonna send it I'm gonna
到十，我要寄给我
transform it such that I'm gonna give it
转换它，让我给它
this expression called payload what's
这个表达式称为有效载荷是什么
gonna what's gonna give me is this
要给我的是这个
message but I don't care about the
讯息，但我不在乎
message itself I care about the payload
消息本身，我关心有效负载
of the message I don't care what the
的消息我不在乎
headers and anything else that spring
标题和其他任何春天
integration gives me on with the payload
集成使我可以承受有效载荷
so I'm saying just take just transform
所以我是说只需要转换
pull out the payload for me now that we
现在我们为我拉出有效载荷
have the payload I want to take that I'm
有我想带走的有效载荷
gonna give it to this thing called a
会给这个叫做a的东西
tweet analyzer which I'm not gonna have
我不会的推特分析器
enough time to show you the code for and
有足够的时间向您展示代码，并且
it really isn't pertinent to the talk
确实与演讲无关
but I'm gonna do some I'm gonna ask some
但是我要去做一些我要去问一些
questions about the tweet I just got and
有关我刚收到的推文的问题，
when I get that tweet I want to hand it
当我收到那条推文时，我想交给它
off to a handler now this is a simple
现在交给处理程序，这很简单
slightly simplified version of the code
略微简化的代码版本
I'm about to show you the handler can do
我将向您展示处理程序可以执行的操作
whatever you want the handler to do
无论您希望处理程序做什么
there's some bad of the box tweet spring
盒子里有一些不好的鸣叫春天
integration handlers I wrote my own for
我为自己编写的集成处理程序
the purposes of this and now the get
现在的目的
finally says build this integration flow
最后说建立这个整合流程
and so when I run it I get to see things
所以当我运行它时，我会看到东西
like this and again this has been
这样，这又是
running there it is this has been
运行在那里，这是
running since around keynote time on
自从大约在主题演讲时间开始运行
Tuesday night and so it's showing that
星期二晚上，这表明
since keynote time we've had 1686 tweets
自从主题演讲以来，我们已经发布了1686条推文
matching spring 1 to G X or s to G X and
将Spring 1匹配到GX或将s匹配到GX并
now there's 1687 I'm using WebSockets to
现在有1687年，我正在使用WebSockets
keep this updated if a new one comes in
如果有新的更新，请保持更新
and the top person tweeting the top 10
和最高的人发推文，排名前十
people tweeting are on the left column
推文的人在左列
in the middle column you have the people
在中间一栏中，您有人员
who are mentioned most often it's not as
最常被提及的人不是
surprising that spring 1 to GX is
令人惊讶的是GX的春天1是
mentioned because it's part of the
提到，因为它是
search criteria
搜索条件
Josh long is number 2 that's also not
乔希·朗（Josh long）是第二个
surprising because he apparently gets
令人惊讶，因为他显然得到了
mentioned quite some bit and he also
提到了很多，他也
tweets quite some bit as you can see
如你所见
from the first column and then the last
从第一列到最后一列
one is the top hashtag so people who are
一个是最热门的标签，
tweeting about spring 1 to G X these are
推文关于GX的春季1
the ones who are most
那些最
tweeting about it and here's the ones
发推文，这是那些
that are mentioned and here's the ones
被提到，这是那些
or here's the hashtags that are
或者这是
appropriate to that and so as you're
合适的，所以你
tweeting this I asked you earlier in the
发推文我早些时候在问你
talk to just tweet about this stuff
只是在推特上谈论这个东西
we're still like 19 away but if you were
我们仍然像19点路程，但如果你是
to certainly start you know tweeting
肯定会开始你知道
about hashtag Spring social like
关于hashtag Spring social like
everybody in this room did that right
这个房间里的每个人都做对了
now you would see spring social come up
现在你会看到春季社交活动来了
on this list over here so go ahead do it
在这里的清单上，所以继续吧
knock yourself out but uh that'd be
yourself倒自己，但是那会是
awesome but yeah what's really
太棒了，但是是真的
interesting is the other night I after
有趣的是我之后的另一个夜晚
the keynote I had this running and I
主题演讲我已经开始运行了，我
left it running it's running on Cloud
让它运行在云上
Foundry right now I left it running I
铸造厂我现在让它运转
haven't touched it since I launched it
自从我推出以来从未动过它
but I was doing some stuff locally with
但是我在当地做一些事情
it just kind of tinkering around with it
它只是在修补它
and so locally I don't have the history
所以在本地我没有历史
that the one running on Cloud Foundry
在Cloud Foundry上运行的那个
has so locally I only see the most
在本地这么多，我最多只能看到
recent tweets I sort of don't have the
我最近没有的推文
history of the older ones Tuesday night
周二晚上的历史
it was really interesting that on the
真的很有趣
far right hand column one of the top
最右手列之一
hashtags was slob I thought that was
主题标签很烂，我认为那是
interesting
有趣
nevertheless I can show you the code the
不过，我可以向您展示代码
actual code for this but it looks a heck
实际的代码，但看起来很麻烦
of a lot like it was on the previous
就像以前的
slide I showed you so I'm gonna move on
我给你看的幻灯片，所以我要继续
real quick because I have a much more
很快，因为我还有更多
important thing I want to talk about
我想谈的重要的事情
before we get out of here and I don't
在我们离开这里之前，我不会
have but like 10 minutes to do that talk
大概有十分钟的时间
about what's happening next in spring
关于明年春季发生的事情
social and so some degree I want to
社会和某种程度上我想
answer that by asking you what's gonna
通过问你会怎么回答
happen next so Oliver tweeted this the
接下来发生，因此Oliver在推特上发布了
other day I thought it was wonderful
前几天，我认为那太好了
that he tweeted this he actually didn't
他在推特上说他实际上没有
write it though he actually got it from
尽管他实际上是从那里得到的
a comment on reddit by someone they met
他们遇到的某人对reddit的评论
bad moon rawson anybody here anybody
坏月亮罗森任何人在这里任何人
here know that person or that person cuz
在这里知道那个人或那个人因为
they're brilliant what they said is
他们说的很棒
great when given a choice they prefer
当他们选择时很棒
spring primarily because of the
春天主要是因为
community and I that's true I mean
社区，这是真的，我的意思是
pretty much Spring has a fantastic
春天几乎有一个梦幻般的
community as evidenced by the thousand
一千所证明的社区
or so people that are here this week and
大概这周在这里的人
the community I feel it a lot in spring
春天给我的感觉很多
social I have like 25 or more community
我喜欢25个或更多社区
led projects and that's great and I get
领导的项目，那很棒，我得到了
a lot of feedback from the community but
来自社区的很多反馈，但是
I'm asking you now to be a part of that
我现在要你加入其中
and be if you're not already be more a
如果你还不是一个
part of that and here's how you can do
部分，这就是你可以做的
that
那
the simplest thing you can possibly do
您可能要做的最简单的事情
is report an issue so you can go to
正在报告问题，因此您可以转到
gerra now some people can also post it
gerra现在有些人也可以发布
to github as a github issue I don't mind
到github作为github问题我不介意
if you do that honestly I would like to
如果您诚实地做到这一点，我想
move away from JIRA but I'm sort of
离开JIRA，但我有点
handcuffed to it for the time being but
暂时戴上手铐
feel free if you want to post something
如果您要发布内容，请放心
to github issues
到github问题
knock yourself out the URL is what you
淘汰自己的网址就是你
see there and if you're posting
看到那里，如果您要发布
something about the core if you're
关于核心的东西，如果你是
posting something about Facebook Twitter
发布有关Facebook Twitter的信息
Linkedin or github you put a put the FB
Linkedin或github您放了FB
or TW whatever at the end of that ask
或TW，无论问到最后
all the questions you want post the
您要发布的所有问题
questions on Stack Overflow and what's
关于堆栈溢出的问题以及什么是
even better about that is if you
更好的是，如果你
answered those questions because any
回答了这些问题，因为
time I spend answering questions is time
我花时间回答问题的时间是时间
I'm not spending doing other other work
我不花钱做其他工作
that like maybe fixing a bug or creating
就像修复错误或创建
a new feature so if you get your head
一个新功能，所以如果您动手
around how this works I encourage you
围绕这是如何工作的，我鼓励你
please as a community help me out I
请作为一个社区帮助我
shouldn't be the only one on spring on
不应该是唯一的春天
Stack Overflow I'm answering all these
堆栈溢出我正在回答所有这些问题
spring social questions feel free to
春季社会问题随时随地
help to try to help me out and get some
帮助尝试帮助我并获得一些帮助
of these answered yourself and
这些回答自己，
thankfully I've had a handful of people
幸好我有几个人
who've done a great job of doing that I
谁做的很棒
would love it if I had more be a part of
如果我能更多地参与其中，我会喜欢的
the community so it's one thing to
社区，这是一回事
submit a bug or to submit a change
提交错误或提交更改
request or an improvement request what's
要求或改进要求是什么
even better do it yourself talk about
最好自己动手谈论
social coding earlier with github Fork
GitHub Fork早期的社交编码
the projects make the changes submit
项目使更改提交
pull requests I would love it if you do
拉请求，如果您愿意，我会喜欢的
that now here's the one thing I have to
现在这是我必须要做的一件事
ask you to actually two things I have to
问你实际上我必须做两件事
ask you to do if you've not done so
请您做是否还没有做
already you have to submit this an
已经您必须提交一个
individual contributor agreement it's
个人贡献者协议
the legal part of this whole thing that
这整个事情的法律部分
they make us make you do
他们让我们让你做
I can't technically merge your full
从技术上讲，我无法合并您的全部
request unless you've done that but if
要求，除非您已这样做，但如果
you've done that then the next thing I
你已经做到了，那么接下来我
ask you to do is make sure you write
问你要做的是确保你写
good tests around your code if you've
如果您已经对代码进行了良好的测试
ever written good test it's gonna make
曾经写好的测试，它将使
it a lot harder for me to do it to merge
我很难合并
that pull requests a lot harder I also
拉力要求更大，我也
encourage you if maybe you don't have
鼓励你，如果你没有
time to submit one of these changes I
是时候提交这些更改之一了
encourage you to look at some of the
鼓励您看一些
pull requests that are out there that
拉在那里的请求
have been submitted and review them for
已提交并对其进行审核
me try them out for me because I can't
我为我尝试一下，因为我做不到
simply hit the merge button in github I
只需点击github中的merge按钮
can't I'm responsible for that code and
我不能为那个代码负责吗
some people don't understand that
有些人不明白
I submitted this yesterday why haven't
我昨天提交了这个为什么没有
you hit the merge button yet because I
您点击了合并按钮，因为我
can't I have to review it I have to I'm
我可以不必复习吗我必须
responsible for that code I have to
负责该代码，我必须
spend some time testing it what would
花一些时间测试它会
help me a ton is if the community tried
如果社区尝试过
some of these things out and left a
这些东西中的一些被遗忘了
comment there yeah I tried this it works
在那发表评论，是的，我尝试了
alright I looked at the code and maybe
好吧，我看了看代码，也许
you know help me out do some of the code
你知道帮我做一些代码
review as well and tell me what-what may
回顾一下，并告诉我可能如何
may be better in that pull request
在拉取请求中可能更好
because if the community is doing this
因为如果社区正在这样做
for me if somebody else in the community
对我来说，如果社区中有人
has reviewed this and said yeah I think
对此进行了审查并说是的，我认为
this is good I've tested it it seems to
这很好，我已经测试过了
do what they say it's gonna do then when
照他们说的去做
I review it I'm still gonna spend time
我查看它，我仍然会花时间
I'm still responsible but I can kind of
我仍然有责任，但我可以
relax a little bit about it I can feel
放松一点，我能感觉到
confident that somebody else is also
相信别人也
giving it a good look I don't have to be
给它一个好的外观，我不必
so strict and focused on it so I
如此严格和专注于我
encourage you as a community help me do
鼓励您作为社区帮助我
that because I'll be plainly honest with
因为我会坦白地说
you the spring team we have a lot of
你们 The Spring Team ，我们有很多
things going on and I had to spend a lot
事情一直在进行，我不得不花很多钱
of time on other projects as well and so
以及其他项目上的时间等等
I don't always get to devote as much
我并不总是那么投入
time to this as I'd like to and so it'd
我想要的时间到了，所以
be helpful if the community does that
如果社区这样做的话会有所帮助
again thankfully we've had a great
再次感谢我们，我们有一个很棒的
community I'm just asking for more
社区我只是在要求更多
participation the last thing I can ask
参与我最后想问的一件事
you to do is contribute in the form of a
您要做的是以
extension if there's some API out there
如果有一些API扩展
that you want an extension for
您想要扩展
contribute so instead of these this list
做出贡献，而不是这些列表
here you can see your own up there you
在这里你可以看到自己的
could add your own project to the list
可以将您自己的项目添加到列表中
and the way you do that is actually
而你这样做的方式实际上是
fourfold there's four steps to it you
有四个步骤
create a service provider take a look at
创建服务提供商看看
this I'm not gonna go over in line by
这我不会排队
line but this is kind of what a very
行，但这是一种非常
basic my peeps if such an API existed my
如果这样的API存在
peep service provider would look like
窥视服务提供商看起来像
take a quick look at it kind of remember
快速浏览一下，记住
what it looks like take a look at it
看起来像什么
later on when you get the slides or
以后当你拿到幻灯片或
viewing this on the video here's what
在视频上观看这是什么
you're going to need a connection
你需要一个连接
factory again take a look that it's
工厂再次看看它是
fairly basic stuff you're looking at the
您正在查看的相当基本的东西
main thing here is you're giving at this
最主要的是您要为此付出
this service provider and giving it an
该服务提供商并为其提供
ID of my peeps
我的窥视ID
that way when connect controller goes to
当连接控制器转到
it you have connect slash my peeps is
如果你有连接斜线我偷看是
the way it handles it you have to create
它必须处理的方式
this API binding which I can't show you
我无法向您显示的此API绑定
code for that because it varies from API
的代码，因为它与API不同
to API everybody's a little different
API的每个人都有点不同
but you create your API binding and then
但是您创建了API绑定，然后
you have to create this little API
您必须创建这个小API
adapter which essentially is the thing
适配器本质上就是这个东西
that gives me the minimal amount of
这给了我最少的
information about the user that's
有关该用户的信息
authorized the application it things
授权应用它的东西
like their screen name their email
喜欢他们的屏幕名称和电子邮件
address whatever the minimal amount of
处理最小的数量
information is
信息是
create one of those once you've created
一旦创建，就创建其中之一
that you've had you basically have the
你已经有了你基本上有
makings of an extension to spring social
春季社交的延伸
tell me about it I will tweet about it
告诉我，我会发推文
to the world
致全世界
put it on github send me the URL I'll
把它放在github上给我发送我会用的URL
tweet about it I'll put it on my next
关于它，我会放在下一个
set of slides it'll be on the spring
一组幻灯片将在春天
social homepage you'll be famous okay
社交首页，你会出名的
and we'll get other people in the
我们会吸引其他人加入
community to step up and try to help you
社区加紧努力为您提供帮助
maintain that now that's still too much
保持现在仍然太多
work in my opinion because if you looked
我认为工作是因为如果你看
at especially slides 1 &amp; 2 that was a
特别是幻灯片1和2
lot of boilerplate code the only thing
很多样板代码唯一
that was different or things like URLs
不一样的东西或类似网址的东西
really and that and the the ID so I've
真的，那个和ID，所以我
got this this thing in work that that's
在工作中得到了这个东西
in the works it's not finished yet I was
在工作中，还没有完成
hoping to have it finished by the time
希望到时候能完成
we got here this weekend or this week it
我们这个周末或这个星期到这里
just didn't happen but I have this this
只是没有发生，但我有这个
thing in the works where ideally you're
理想情况下你在工作中的事情
gonna be able to do something like this
能够做这样的事情
you're gonna be able to configure an
您将能够配置一个
application that you Amalur application
您的Amalur应用程序
of properties spring social providers my
的物业春天社会提供者我
peeps give it an ID authorization URL is
peeps给它一个ID授权URL是
here the token URL is here and here's an
这是令牌URL，这是一个
API binding class that you can use
您可以使用的API绑定类
ideally that's where I want to go with
理想情况下，这就是我想去的地方
this so rather than go through those
这样，而不是经历那些
last four slides rather than create a
最后四张幻灯片，而不是创建一张
service provider rather than create a
服务提供商，而不是创建一个
connection factory you do this and I'm
连接工厂，你这样做，我
gonna leverage the existing work I've
可以利用我现有的工作
already done with generic connection
通用连接已经完成
factories to automatically configure
工厂自动配置
these for you that's where I'm headed
这些给你的就是我要去的地方
with this it's just not quite ready yet
到现在还没有准备好
in the worst case scenario by the way is
在最坏的情况下
if you fail to my goal is if you fail to
如果你失败了我的目标就是
give me an API binding class I'll give
给我一个API绑定类
you a rest template as your API binding
您将休息模板作为API绑定
if you tell me an API binding class then
如果您告诉我一个API绑定类，那么
I'll use that instead that's what spring
我会用那代替那是春天
will give you here's a few other things
会给你一些其他的东西
that are in progress I mentioned the
在进行中，我提到了
simpler extension model I'm looking for
我正在寻找更简单的扩展模型
even tighter spring boots support
更紧密的 spring boot 支撑
actually that that parenthesis and that
实际上那个括号和那个
first bullet belongs on the second
第一颗子弹属于第二颗
bullet I don't know what I was doing
我不知道我在做什么
there but specifically right now it has
在那里，但现在特别是
support auto auto configuration support
支持自动自动配置支持
for provider signing controller
用于提供商签名控制器
I want to detect that you're using
我想检测您正在使用
spring security and give you social
Spring Security 保障，带给您社交
authentication filter instead in that
身份验证过滤器代替
scenario there is a some talk between me
场景我之间有一些谈话
and some of the other guys about getting
还有一些其他的关于
a tighter integration with Spring
与Spring更紧密的集成
Security OAuth taking some of the stuff
安全OAuth吸收了一些东西
that's kind of duplicated between the
这在
two projects and kind of unifying those
两个项目，并统一那些项目
so we're gonna we're going to talk about
所以我们要谈论
that here at some point I do when I
我在某个时候做的事情
mentioned early
提早
add some more proper open ID Connect
添加一些更合适的开放ID Connect
support and I've started thinking a lot
支持，我已经开始思考很多
about number of questions recently about
关于最近的问题数量
stateless connections especially when
无状态连接，尤其是当
you have like a JavaScript client that
您就像一个JavaScript客户端
wants to basically get these tokens but
想要基本上获得这些代币，但是
doesn't want or maybe even wants to
不想甚至可能不想
share them with other applications and
与其他应用共享
so I've got JWT in my mind when I do
所以当我这样做的时候，我会想到JWT
that so I'm this is very fuzzy at the
所以我在这很模糊
moment but is something I've been
片刻，但我一直在
thinking about and that's it I'm out of
想着，就是我没了
I'm Adam slides amount of content and
我是亚当幻灯片内容，
thank you once again to take a look at
再次谢谢你看看
spring social there's reading find it on
春季社交，正在阅读中找到它
the spring dot IO website there's a
spring dot IO网站上有一个
couple of other sessions mildly related
其他几个会话有轻微的相关性
to this talk as far as it goes with
就这个话题
spring integration unfortunately they
Spring Integration 不幸的是他们
both took place yesterday
都发生在昨天
so you missed them but the videos will
所以你错过了他们，但视频会
be online so I went ahead mentioned them
上网，所以我继续提到他们
anyway other than that thank you very
无论如何，非常感谢你
much have a great rest of the conference
这次会议有很多事情要做
the next two sessions you got thank you
接下来的两节你会谢谢
you
您